Remember when Johnson and Johnson was
deemed the like Slytherin of the
vaccines? Remember that? Because eight
people got blood clots. Meanwhile, every
woman on birth control is like, "Yeah,
it gives me heart palpitations. Sure."
But Brian says condoms make him cheat,
so [\h__\h] it. Okay. [laughter]
That's an impression of my [\h__\h] sister.
That's who that is. [laughter]
She is a [\h__\h] You don't know her. I'll
tell you. Speaking of abortions, she
called me and she was like, "Jordan, I'm
pregnant." And I was like, "Don't worry
about it, babe. I'll come up state.
We'll open a bottle of wine, have an
abortion party as per us." Right. And
she goes, "I'm keeping it." And I, Dude,
the first words out of my mouth. I was
like, "In a jar or what?" [laughter]
I was like, "They don't let you do that.
There's no way."
I had a guy come inside me recently.
That was scary. Have you guys had this
happen? No. This [\h__\h] idiot. I'm
[\h__\h] I'm 31 years old. When somebody
gets close, I'm like a trained house
cat. I roll over, I show him my belly.
I'm like, "Right there. That's where
that goes."
This thing came inside me and I was
like, "Yo, what happened?" And he goes,
"I don't know. I guess he got too
excited." I was like, "Please don't talk
about this. Like, your kid threw up in
my Honda Civic, you piece of [\h__\h]
I'm done with sex, though. I'm off sex
for now. I just went through a breakup.
Anybody else?" No. Me neither.
[laughter]
No, I'm doing okay. I'm all right. I put
a sweet potato in the oven last night
for like 8 minutes or so until it was
lukewarm and then I took it out and I
held on to it until I fell asleep. So,
[laughter]
we're doing good.
Dude, I go through so many breakups. My
life is like organized by like epochs of
men. It's like biblical at this point.
It's like Matthew 2013. [laughter]
Thou shalt not lay with a man who yells,
"Let's go when he comes." You know what
I mean? [laughter]
I got to chill.
You know what's fun? You know how when
somebody dumps you, all your buddies
start coming in with mental diagnosis of
the person? You know what I mean? All my
friends are like, "He's a narcissist
with Asberers." [laughter]
I'm like, "What does that say about me,
dude?
What do you think? I'm just hanging
outside of special needs courses, luring
these guys in, dangling Nintendo
Switches in front of my [\h__\h] [\h__\h] you.
[laughter]
I do go through a lot of breakups. I'm
difficult to date. I was I intimidate
men. I'm a comedian. I used to be a
contractor. It's a whole thing. Okay.
[laughter]
I was raised by a pack of lesbians.
That's why I'm like this. All right.
I've tried dating women a million times.
I can't do it. I'm too OCD. The hottest
thing a woman can say like, "I'm so
wet." I'm like, "Well, clean yourself
up, you animal. Jesus."
I do have OCD. I bet I tried taking
Prozac for OCD. Have you guys tried
Prozac? No. You live in California. [\h__\h]
you. [laughter]
I live in New York. Okay, we're all on
it. You can't come on Prozac. It's
impossible. All right, you get to the
top of the roller coaster, you got to go
back down the way you came. It's a
nightmare. [laughter]
I was on Prozac for OCD, but I couldn't
come. So, I got off Prozac, and now I
can come, but I have to do it in like
multiples of three or my mother will
die. You know what I mean? [laughter]
I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm in therapy. Are
you guys in therapy? Do you guys do
therapy here? Yes. Okay. I hate it. I
hate my therapist so much. She's 14
years old. I want her to die. Okay. I
hate her. You know why I hate her? Every
time I log onto the Zoom therapy thing,
her hair is always soaking wet. It
drives me insane. She's like, "How was
your weekend?" I'm like, "Good. How was
your [\h__\h] shower? What are we doing?"
[laughter]
She's also way younger than me, so I've
seen way more [\h__\h] than she has. I've
made her cry way more than she's seen me
cry. I swear to God. There was a point a
couple weeks ago where I was describing
my childhood and I swear to God she
almost said the words, you know, you
need to get help for this. Seriously.
>> Yeah, it is hard. It's hard to date
being a female comedian because boys are
always worried that we're going to roast
your little pen on stage. You guys hate
that. But we do that offstage as well. I
can draw your dick by looking into her
eyes. You understand that? [laughter]
>> It's true. We love to do it. You guys
hate it. I know you do. I'm pretty sure
that's how witches got started. You know
what I mean? I think some dude in the
1400s pulled his dick out and was like,
"What do you think?" And she was like,
"Are you [\h__\h] serious, dude?" And he
was like, "BURN HER." [laughter] That's
why they think they fly around on
broomsticks cuz she was just with her
buddies being like, "It was this
skinny." I swear to God it was this
skinny. [laughter]
Anyway, I'm I think I'm going to chill
on dating for a while. My therapist said
I should. I hate her. I hate her so
much. You know what she said to me? This
[\h__\h] Okay. She goes, "Okay, just
imagine." She's looking at me. She's 9
years old, right? She's got the mascara.
[\h__\h] You know what I mean? She goes,
"Jordan, I think you have abandonment
trauma." And I was like, "What?" And she
goes, "And I think you should consider
seeing a more experienced therapist." I
was like, "You [\h__\h] buttthead. That's
the definition of triggering, right?
That's like if a crazy person comes into
your office and you go, hey, I think you
have schizophrenia." And they go,
"What?" And you go, "Nothing. Did you
hear something?" I didn't hear anything.
She [laughter] says,
"She got mad at me the other day cuz I
jumped on the apps right after the
breakup." Do you guys have Hinge out
here?
Do you? Hinge sucks. I hate Hinge. It's
where all the woke cowboys go. You know
what I mean? They all have like, "Don't
tread on me snake" tattoos, but then
they're like, "This is my cat, Malcolm
X," or whatever the [\h__\h] [laughter]
And this guy that I match, he was
convinced I was a lesbian. What
happened? He saw my truck. Okay, I'll
give him that. [laughter]
I think that this guy, he saw my truck
and he goes, "Why do you have a truck?"
And I was like, "I used to do carpentry
for a living." And I swear to God, he
goes, "Like Jesus."
[laughter] I was like, "More like Jesus,
if I'm being honest.
>> [laughter]
>> All right. So, he sees my truck. There's
tools in my truck. I think my bowling
ball is in there. Okay. [laughter]
So, what happens is, all right, full
disclosure, I was on mushrooms for this
date. Okay, I'm just going to be upfront
with you guys. [laughter]
And he wrote that he was 5'9" in his
bio, but he was really 5'6 or under.
Okay? And I'm fine with a short king,
but I was on drugs, right? [laughter]
So, as he was walking up to me, I was
like, "Is my depth perception off?"
[laughter]
I was like, "Shouldn't he be getting
bigger as he approaches me?" [laughter]
Okay.
So, me and this guy, we sit down and
we're talking. I'm on mushrooms. He's
short as hell. [laughter]
And he keeps talking about the Venice
bianale. Do you guys know what that is?
Okay. Me neither. My two people. All
right. But I had heard of the Whitney
bienial that happens in New York. And
he's like, "The bianale? The bonoli? The
b." And I was like, "Dude, are you
trying to say the word bianial by any
chance?" [laughter]
And he goes, "That's in English. In
Italian, the word is bianale." The
mushrooms hit me so hard. I started flop
sweating and I was like, "Have we been
speaking Italian this whole time?"
[laughter]
I was like, I don't know any Italian.
I did [\h__\h] that guy, though. [laughter]
You know what happened with that guy?
Okay. All right.
So, me and this guy, we get into my
truck. We go back to his house. Okay.
And we're hooking up. We're having
smashy sex, right? Do you guys know what
smashy sex is? All right. In your 20s,
sex is all about seamless transition
changes, right? It's like we went from
the bed to the carpet to the desk with
the dick in me. The It's like a
community play. All right.
In your 30s, you don't care about any of
that. You're just smack. You don't care.
Okay? You ever watch a boxing match or
an MMA fight? You know that moment in
boxing when they're beating the [\h__\h] out
of each other and then somehow at the
same time they both get really tired out
and just simultaneously agree to lean on
each other for a minute or two? You know
what I'm talking about? It's the cutest
thing I've ever seen. But that that is
30 and up sex where you're like, I'm
going to rip you apart in a minute, dog,
but you got to take my weight, brother.
You got to hold me up.
>> [laughter]
>> It's because your priorities change,
right? In your 20s, you care about like
what your tits look like on top. And
once you hit 30, you're like, "Dude,
just hit my cervix so hard that I forget
my father's dying." Okay.
[laughter]
Okay. So, what happens is
we're having the smashy sex, right? And
then my knee goes right through his
drywall. Oopsie poopsy.
It's happened before. It'll happen
again. [laughter]
And I was like very chivalous. I was
like, "Don't worry about it, buddy. I
have spackle in my truck.
>> [laughter]
>> And then he goes he goes, "I'm sorry. I
just feel like I need to check in really
quick. Are you sure? Are you sure you're
not gay?" And I immediately drop into
the deep coach's stance and was like,
"All right, listen up, little guy."
Okay. [laughter]
I was like, "I just had your dick in my
mouth for like 10 minutes, right?" And
he was like, "Yeah." I was like, "Okay,
you should take a look around." And he
was like, "Why is that?" And I was like,
"Cuz you're the one [\h__\h] the
handyman." Okay. Are you sure you're not
gay, [\h__\h] All right. I love you
guys so much. Enjoy the rest OF THE
SHOW.
WHAT WAS EVERYBODY'S UH favorite
quarantine purchase? What did y'all buy?
>> What? Henny? You just said henny? My
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] bro. The [\h__\h] I'm talking
about. He just was like, I'm going
[\h__\h] get drunk this entire pandemic
[laughter] and I'mma marry a black
woman. That's what I Hell yes. And he
got the pearls. I know you [\h__\h] black
[\h__\h] Anyway, that's weird. That's
weird. That's rude. Um,
[laughter]
that's rude. That's rude. Swagy ass
dude. Henny. What else? What else did
you guys buy?
>> I found a weed.
>> Plants. Weed. Oh, [\h__\h] San Diego,
right? [laughter]
Plants and weed. I bought a bet. So,
>> I bought a bet. You know, you know,
while y'all were getting all [\h__\h]
weird and buying [\h__\h] toilet paper
all the time, I was walking around all
holy and [\h__\h]
It was great. You got a bet, dog? You
been thinking about it?
>> Yeah.
>> Change your life, bro. [laughter] I can
tell you don't have a bet because you
don't have the glow about you.
>> [laughter]
>> N I got up a day and like everybody got
all my [\h__\h] got mad at me and just
like, "Oh, okay [\h__\h] you just you just
cool with having water shoot up your
booty hole, dog. Sounds a little spicy
to me, bro." And I'm like, "No, it's
not." You know, we could have been beded
bros, but you chose to be toxic both
physically and mentally. [laughter] I
think that's why I'm trying to get rid
of toxic masculinity uh so that I can
just powerwash my [\h__\h] in peace.
[laughter]
Is that weird?
I don't know, man. I think we're getting
better with the toxic stuff, dudes,
fellas. [laughter] Yeah,
>> little bit.
>> Little bit. A little bit. We call each
other gay differently. Have you noticed
that? [laughter]
Like before it was like, "Oh, are you
gay, nigga?" or whatever. But that's
like [\h__\h] up. You don't want to say
that to somebody. Now it's like, "Um,
hey, can I talk to you FOR A SECOND?
>> [laughter]
>> UH ME AND THE BROS UH WE'VE been
watching you and uh how you like to play
defense hella close and whatnot and
[laughter]
we just wanted to say
we think you gay [\h__\h] Like it's it's
just different, right? Before it was
like an insult. Now it's like concern
like yo let's go get you some dick. Like
who cares? [laughter]
Before it was no homo. Now it's pause.
Like, let's put a pause in this
conversation [laughter] because you just
said that your favorite snack was salted
nuts and we just wanted to know
[laughter]
what did you mean by that?
Cuz at the end of the day, it's not
about insulting your bros. It's about
starting a dialogue, you know.
[laughter]
Oh god.
Um, I'm I'm from Los Angeles, born and
raised, and um I don't recommend it.
>> [laughter]
>> Don't don't raise your kids there cuz I
I I don't know. Like here's what
happens. All your friends will just get
like forced out of the city and then it
just gets filled with people not from
there that talk [\h__\h] about the city that
raised you like in your face like [\h__\h]
you. [\h__\h] everything about LA. I hate
the food. I hate the traffic. Why is
there so much traffic? [\h__\h] you
you're why. You're the one that chose to
move to a city that's been at capacity
for the past 20 years. [laughter] And I
say 20 years, that's exactly how long it
takes people to realize that dreams
don't come true. Like, stop [laughter]
[\h__\h] moving here. Oh, all LA culture
is is kale smoothies. No, it's not. LA
culture is going to a kickback, stepping
on someone's Jordans, getting shot at,
and then relieving that near-death
experience with a nice kale smoothie.
Like, that's [laughter] what [\h__\h] is.
I got jumped down the street from the
Seas Chocolate Factory. Like this [\h__\h]
[laughter] is it's very weird, you know?
It's just delicious chocolate wafting
everywhere and then somebody standing
over you like, "Ain't [\h__\h] sweet,
nigga?" Like, [laughter]
bro, the air is literally sweet, dog.
Like,
it's so It's such a [\h__\h] bad place,
man. [laughter]
Family moved there from Trinidad and
Tobago. You guys know where that is?
>> Yeah, Trinity. Did I say? Oh, you Triny.
That's what's up. Oh, that's [\h__\h]
crazy. [laughter]
We got a Trinidadian Mario dog. Like,
you know what? You know how much
representation that [\h__\h] is, bro? Oh my
god. Mario's got like a red and black
like big Triny Ting boy. Like, any
anyway. Anyway, anyway, [laughter]
that's dope. My family's from Trinidad
and my family are still there. I don't I
don't [\h__\h] with them. Like, they're
mean. They're mean. Like, just imagine
an an entire family just filled with
like Jamaican restaurant cashiers. Like,
they're all mean as [\h__\h] for no reason.
They just call the house and just talk
[\h__\h] It's like, "Oh, you guys are all
dumb. Americans are all stupid." I'm
like, "Bro, you called me from a flip
phone, dog. Why am I supposed to respect
you? You know, I'm not rich, but I can
pretty sure just move there and be your
king. Like, show me some [laughter]
some respects.
This next joke is [\h__\h] gross, but
like [\h__\h] it. Who cares? [laughter]
So, um, I was seeing a girl that was
also from Trinidad, which is a really
small island. Um, and she had the same
last name as some of my cousins, but we
proved that she wasn't my cousin. Like,
[\h__\h] you guys. We prove that. [laughter]
We prove that.
But, um, I did sleep with her before I
was sure. And I'm not, you know,
[laughter]
I'm not proud of that. But in that
moment, I understood the South. It's
like, I get y'all. You know, trying
[laughter] to keep that ignorance bliss,
bro.
Cuz you realize the only difference
between sleeping with someone and that
someone being your third cousin is too
many questions. [laughter]
That joke is called Schrodinger's [\h__\h]
Anyway, [laughter]
anyway,
so race jokes are next. But like, okay,
here's [laughter]
here's the I don't think I deserve race
takes at all. You know, I I don't know.
I I just listen to whatever black women
tell me to do on Twitter and I just, you
know, [laughter] do that. I was like
raised in like a middle class black
neighborhood. So, like imagine if I got
on stage and I was just like, "You know
what? The white man is trying to keep us
down and keep us in poverty and out the
back you heard that [\h__\h] had a pool
growing up. Like, don't [\h__\h]
[laughter]
listen to me. You're an idiot.
I could be like a I don't know, like a
sacrifice or some [\h__\h] like that." Like
I you know, like cuz listen, if I got
beat up by the cops, that nigga's going
to jail. Cuz listen, if he went to court
and he was like, "Well, your honor, I
perceived him as a threat." And the
judge is like, "Fuck you. You're telling
me that that little dimple [\h__\h] was a
threat to you? You're telling me that
the black Shirley Temple had anything on
him but a [\h__\h] lollipop? Are you out
of your [\h__\h] mind?"
I family in Denver. That's like the
whitest place [laughter] of all time.
They have a kitchen island. They're
doing fine. They're doing like
big things. [laughter]
I wanted to visit them not too long ago.
And uh pretty much all I did was like
pick up my 9-year-old cousin from
school, which was fine, but I didn't
really like [\h__\h] with the way the
administrators kept like following me
around the whole time, like ask me
dumbass questions like, "Oh, what are
you doing here? Who are you here to pick
up?" I'm like, "We're in Denver, bro.
Like the only other [\h__\h] What are you
talking about?" So, I got mad at her cuz
like she's basically accusing me of like
wanting to touch kids. Like that's not
even a black crime. You know, y'all do
that. That's your [laughter] [\h__\h]
I'm statistically I'm sorry. I'm
[laughter] sorry. BUT YOU KNOW, I'M NOT
trying to say that only white people
touch kids, but I am saying check the
scoreboard, [\h__\h] Like, it's very
[laughter] obvious. [applause]
It was like y'all first cuz the whole
Catholicism thing really patted the
numbers. [laughter]
Then second is uncles in general.
And then R. Kelly's third. R. Kelly.
[laughter] He did a lot.
But I don't know, man. Like, [laughter]
I don't think I I I, you know, all I can
do is just give, you know, black
conspiracy theories. That's all I have.
[laughter]
Like, here's my favorite one that I
created. Series of questions for you
guys. First question, did you guys know
that Caucasians get peanut allergies
more than any other race? Did you guys
know that?
>> Woo. [laughter]
It's just a black lady JUST BE LIKE,
"WOO!" YEAH, [laughter] DAMN.
YEAH,
they get peanut allergies more than any
other race. Second question. Did you
guys know that peanut butter is a
leading cause of peanut allergy
outbreaks? Did you guys know that?
>> No.
>> Oh, no. It makes sense. Third and final
question. Do you think that George
Washington Carver
made peanut butter to slowly kill white
people? Because I believe that [\h__\h]
100%, dog. He made over a hundred
different uses for peanuts and on the
seventh day he made peanut butter and
was like, I [\h__\h] got him. You know,
[laughter] like first black inventor.
More like first black evil genius. He
was born a slave and died free because
he killed his master with something
scrumptious. How does that All right,
[laughter] guys. That was my song. Thank
you so [cheering] much.
>> Hey, HOW'S IT GOING, LA?
>> HELL YEAH. You guys drinking tonight?
>> You should be. That's what's up. Uh, I
love drinking so much, but the problem
is that when I drink too much, I do this
thing where I drunk text people that
want relationships with me,
and I don't want [\h__\h] to do with them.
So, what ends up happening is I go out,
I drink too much, and then I start drunk
texting my mom and [laughter]
gets weird, you know, then once she
figures out to text me back with her
index finger cuz what they that's what
they do, you know? I'm like, it's too
late. I'm sober. You know what I'm
saying? [laughter]
But, uh, my mom was very strict on
education. And so, uh, kids always tease
me. They call me a white girl cuz I can
read and [\h__\h] And every day they tease
me and they'd be like, "Leah, you talk
like a white person in a sorority." And
I'm like, "Damn, that's crazy. I do love
saying nigga." Uh, no. My mom my mom was
very strict on me growing up. She was so
strict on me. Uh, she kicked me off the
soccer team because I got a 89 in math.
>> No.
>> Yeah. She was like, "The plan was all
A's." A's. A B was not the plan. Which
makes sense coming from a woman that has
three children by three different men. I
don't think B was ever the plan
[laughter]
or affordable. Like, [laughter]
it's okay. I escaped. I'm out of
therapy. I'm not in therapy [laughter]
no more. I'm not in it. I don't need it.
I'm not depressed no more. Thank you.
[laughter] Yeah. I no longer have
depression, y'all.
>> Yeah. Thank you. Of course. Oh, thanks.
Yeah, cuz I no longer have health
insurance.
But you know what? Now that I'm 27, I
feel like I'm engaging in 27 activities,
you know, especially as a woman. Like
watching true crime documentaries. You
know what I'm saying? Hell yeah. I've
been watching a lot of true crime cuz
I'm trying to learn how to date. And
[laughter]
and I'll tell you this, dating it has
it's brought the f- word into my life
tremendously. Okay. Fear. Uh is there
I'm just kidding. Food. Here's the
thing. [laughter]
Dating has been my number one source of
being fed. That's the pro. That's the
pro of dating. Okay. The con is when
they cut you off. You know, you know, I
went through a breakup and and you know,
I went through all the side effects of
it. You know, I was like dizzy and
crying all the time, malnutrition cuz I
didn't have no one to feed me for free
anymore. [laughter]
So, I had to be a boss, you know, and I
had to download all these food apps, you
know, and [\h__\h] like Tinder and,
[laughter]
you know, Grinder when I wanted brunch.
It was, [laughter]
it was a lot. [laughter] But, you know
what? I will say this, as I'm getting
older, I can I can take responsibility
for my, you know, my actions in dating,
you know, like I used to have a type
which always messed me up, you know,
like I had a type where I like dudes
whose tattoos described who they were.
Okay, nobody else grew without a father.
Weird. So,
but I I did I like a dude that like a
tattoo of like, you know, like a like a
crab, you know, cuz he was a cancer, you
know, or like, you know, a tattoo of
like Chinese symbols cuz he was
American.
>> [laughter]
>> I [clears throat] I but I've also
realized that I take a lot of stuff. I
do I just I deal with so much [\h__\h] you
know? Like fellas, come on. Y'all know
the differences between both holes.
Okay, you do. Please. Y'all know the
whole one of them is for child birth and
the other one's for marriage. Y'all
know. [laughter]
Cut it out. I'm sick of this weird Red
Rover [\h__\h] that keeps happening. And
then you're like, "Well, THE LIGHTS WERE
OFF. YOU TURNED THEM OFF. WHY ARE YOU
BEING WEIRD?" LIKE,
you know, that's my butthole. You feel
those teeth. Um, [laughter]
but no, like this one dude was like,
"Hey, come over." And I was like, "Cool.
I could eat." And [laughter]
sure. He's like, "Are you one of them
type of girls?" I'm like, "A [\h__\h] that
want to survive?" Absolutely. [laughter]
And those will be the same type of dudes
that want you to ride them for a long
ridiculous amount of time. Ain't got no
electrolytes in the fridge. Like it's
ridiculous. You want me to ride you when
you know that high air rises? I'mma die.
Like I don't [laughter]
Yeah, I'm single. But
I've also realized like I love sensitive
dudes. I like sensitive dudes. I do. Art
majors. No. Okay. I love I love
sensitive men. I love when men cry, bro.
Like that's I think it's wonderful. I
love when men cry so much I try to
record it. Um,
[laughter]
but I can never really capture what I
need in time cuz I can never unlock my
phone quick enough. You know what I
mean? [laughter] Cuz my face recognition
doesn't recognize me when I'm happy.
[laughter]
Yeah. I love being lied to. That's
another one. I love it. I love being
lied to. But I will say this, as I'm
getting older, I'm learning what these
lies are and I'm starting to call them
out a lot quicker. You know, this one
dude I hit up and I was like, "Hey, what
you doing?" He's like, "Oh, nothing."
You know, I was like, "Really? I hear
some noises in the background." You
know, he's like, "Oh, it's the TV." I
was like, "Nigga, you got no TV. Like,
what's up? Talk to me. What's going on?"
He's like, "All right, you got me. I'm
in Dubai." [laughter]
I was like, "No, you're not.
You're not in Dubai." And I know you're
not in Dubai because I hear [\h__\h] in
the background. They sound free. YOU'RE
NOT [laughter]
IN DUBAI.
It's ridiculous. [laughter]
Which is why I think women are better
liars. Okay. I do. Right. Which is why I
think that women really should be
present. I think
I think it's ridiculous that that's even
still a a topic of discussion. Like, of
course, women should be president. But
what's funny, I'll say this. A lot of
the stereotypes of why women should not
be president are so played out. And
granted, I love a good stereotype,
especially if it gets me out of being
the driver for it. [laughter] But, but I
just feel like the excuses for why women
shouldn't be president are so played
out. Like, they be like, "Oh, women talk
too much." Like, you know, dude, anytime
a man's ever said that a woman talks too
much, she told him no. Uh,
[laughter]
or they say like women are too
emotional. Anytime a woman has ever been
called too emotional, she told a man,
"Uh, stop." Um,
or they [laughter]
or they say, "You know, we crazy." No,
bro. Like, no, that's not that's not
accurate. Anytime a man's ever called a
woman crazy. All she did was go to his
house at 1:32 a.m., he didn't pick up
the phone. So, she went around the back
and went to his window. And just like
his her heart, her fist is heavy. So she
tapped and broke that [\h__\h] and jumped
on top of him to make sure that he was
not cheated or dead. So
I think men know the problem.
I think those are all great attributes
for a president. I really do if you ask
me. Yeah. But talks too much. Of course
I don't want my president to shut the
[\h__\h] up about the change they want in
their country. You know emotional? No.
Passionate. I want my president to have
passion right about change in the
country. uh crazy, adamant. Uh
[laughter]
I don't know. I just feel like if I was
president, you know, yeah, I' absolutely
I'd go overseas and I'd go to the
embassy or wherever dictators lay and I,
you know, knock on the door, have them
open. I'll look him in the eyes and I'd
be like, "Yo,
where are we?
[laughter]
Gas prices are rising. Are you mad at
me? [laughter]
seem a little distant.
Sorry about that broken window. I didn't
know if you were cheating on me with
Russia or dead. Um,
>> yeah. No, I think I think women women
are fantastic and and I feel like men
are starting to like, you know, support
uh that we uh can like uh talk um and
you know, it's crazy like during the you
know, during the pandemic. Did you maybe
this is a little outdated, but I just
want to see how you guys feel. Did y'all
have a good co
>> [laughter]
>> Okay. Yeah, I I'm sorry. I had a great
time. I did I had a great co because all
my enemies are over 50. Um [laughter]
but what's you know interesting is you
know I had a lot of support. Uh there
was this man uh that supported me
creating a only fans uh anybody in the
service industry. I
and and he was like hey I'm you know I'm
I'm rooting for you. I see you women
empowerment. And that's what men say
when they want to [\h__\h] you uh for the
free. And [laughter]
and it it threw me off cuz I hadn't seen
this man since high school. You know
what I mean? I hadn't seen him since
high school cuz he was my old algebra
teacher,
[laughter]
which really upset me cuz I'm like,
where was his energy when you failed me?
You know what I mean? Same titties. Um
no, but dating's fine. You date whoever
you want, whoever, you know, pays the
bill. I will say this.
>> [laughter]
>> You know, are you at in interracial
dating? Are you into interracial dating?
Cool. Okay. Yeah. This side. No. They're
like, "No, we're going to keep it in the
family. I feel you, brother."
And those of you that are into
interracial dating, good for you. So is
Thomas Jefferson. Here's my thing.
I I don't discriminate, okay, against
money. But I [laughter]
People always ask me, is there like a
difference, you know? And here's the
thing. You got to broaden your horizon
if you want to be happy uh with a
person. And you know, like for me
personally, when it comes to race,
there's really no difference if I did
like a black guy or a white guy. Um
except for like if I take my wig off in
front of them for the first time. Okay.
So like for instance, I'll go with a
black dude, take my wig off in front of
him, he's like, "Ooh, br it's cold
little Bill." And then we're having a
good time.
[laughter]
White guy a little different. We go off
for the night. We have a good time. I
bring him back to my place. I have a
nice little cup of milk waiting for him
and uh [laughter]
and I and I take off my wig and he's
just like, "Oh my gosh." And I'm like,
"Yeah, it's a wig. Sorry, boo." You
know, [laughter]
he's like, "No, you don't have to
explain anything to me." The queen. Um
he's like, "But you could have told me
that you know you have cancer."
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, it's [\h__\h] up. I pretend to have
cancer for a free meal. Uh, I've been
Leah Samson, guys. Thank you very much.
Have a wonderful night. [cheering]
>> I made more money in 2020 than I've ever
made in a single year in my entire life.
[cheering] Thank you. It was cuz I was
on unemployment [laughter]
and I got those stimmies, baby. Those
stemmies.
M
I always thought comedy was filling the
vast emptiness I feel inside. I just
never tried money. That's better. Way
better. Who cares how funny you are?
Let's go to Cheesecake. [laughter]
Tell me a joke, clown.
Clown.
I went home during the pandemic, but I
had to leave cuz my mom's boyfriend
moved in. And he keeps trying to be my
friend. And we love Terry, but pick a
lane. You know, he's always like, "Hey,
let's be friends. What can I do to be
your friend? Like you could stop having
sex with my mom. [laughter]
I don't ask much from my friends, TERRY.
[laughter]
I might have to draw the line. It's not
a quality I'm looking for. [laughter]
And a friend, glad you're doing it. Glad
you're banging my mom, but we don't need
a kayak. You know,
why would I, a guy who has friends that
don't bang my mom, take on you?
someone who does indeed logistically
make it make sense.
You know, it's funny. I did go kayaking
with Terry. That's my guy. I love Terry.
[laughter]
I sat my mom down. I was like, "What are
your intentions with my friend Terry?"
It's cool that you're dating my friend.
I'm glad you make him happy, but if you
hurt him,
[laughter] cuz I have my friend's backs.
You know, it's weird being his friend,
though. Some It's like, you know, at
least when your dad's banging your mom,
he's like, "Go to bed.
do your homework. You're like, "Ah,
you're the man. I'm afraid of you." But
Terry bangs my mom. He's like, "Hey, you
want to smoke a bowl?" No. [laughter]
I mean, I'll take a ri. Come on.
And just smoking post sex bowls with
Terry. [laughter]
Out there ripping a sativa with Tear
Bear. Come on. [laughter]
He'll be my third dad if he can lock it
down. But he won't. That's the thing. I
know it. He doesn't have it. And now
that I'm his friend, I feel I should be
like, "Dude, friend to friend, get the
[\h__\h] out of here. [laughter]
We'll hang out later, but I don't want
her hurting you." But I do want a third
dad. That'd be so cool. First dad
relationship, boring, very lesson based,
a lot of yelling. Second dad, he'll try
to be like serious one time, but they
have no power. You know, one time he'll
be like, "Hey man, could you not do
that?" You're like, "You're not my dad."
He's like, "I guess doing that's all
right." [laughter]
Stepdads are like those stop lights
before the freeway where you're like,
I'm probably just going to go.
[laughter]
>> I don't recognize your authority at all.
Two cars per green. [\h__\h] 10 cars per
green. [laughter] It's the freeway last
I checked. Mine America.
[laughter]
I want to be a dad, but I'm afraid of
ruining my child. I think we all have
that that fear because I think parents,
you just forget what it's like to be a
kid. You give bad advice. My dad's
advice to keep me off drugs was if
anyone ever offers you drugs, just tell
them, "Hey, my dad doesn't think drugs
are cool." And walk away. [laughter]
I was like, "I'll just overdose."
Don't want to say that to someone who
could see me twice in my [laughter]
lifetime.
I'm afraid of having a son that could
beat me up.
That's pretty freaky. [laughter]
I'm just like, "Hey kiddo, how's the
homework coming along?" He just beats
the [\h__\h] out of you. [laughter]
Are there any parents in the audience?
>> You played a lot of video games over the
pandemic, maybe with your children, I
don't know. [laughter]
But they're full of hate. I think you
should know your kids are full of hatred
and they hate me specifically. One kid
told me I played like my nipples were
too low. [laughter]
Nine months nine months ago this
happened. Every day I get out of the
shower and I look in the mirror
[laughter]
might be a little low.
And I have body issues all by myself. I
don't need kids.
I can't grow a beard. I'm almost 28.
Been doing No Shave November since
January 31st, 1994. [laughter]
And it's frustrating cuz look at this.
Look at this. Cameras, get a look. Zoom.
What is this? [laughter] What is this?
We got hair. We can grow hair. That's
not the issue. It's where we grow the
hair. [laughter]
Wherever I don't want a beard, there's a
beard.
>> [laughter]
>> my ass. [\h__\h] you.
Anyone? Anyone in this parking lot? You
think you have more hair on your ass
than I do? Let's go out there after the
show. [laughter]
Slap some cash on the sidewalk, tough
guy.
Pull our pants down on three like an old
western shootouts. [laughter]
It's I trick you with the face. I'm like
a pool hustler. I get you in like I'm a
pro. [laughter]
It's insane looking in my ass. The
forest of black hair. It's like when you
close your eyes. [laughter]
I hear a crunch when I sit on stuff.
It's the real deal. [laughter]
It's the real deal, baby. It's an issue
every day.
I shaved it once when I was 12 cuz I was
like horny and I think it came back
extra fierce. [laughter]
That's what they say happens.
Puberty.
Puberty is crazy.
Pi is crazy because you're just this kid
that likes baseball and the color orange
and then you wake up one day and you're
like, I'd [\h__\h] that couch. [laughter]
That's weird.
I [\h__\h] that couch, though.
I'm going to tell a story now and it
doesn't have a ending and it's kind of
gross. So, I'm sorry. But [laughter]
the acts Yeah. The first time I ever
watched online pornography, my father
caught me. I was I was in the sixth
grade and I was losing my mind. I was so
horny. I was taking a lot of Adderall at
the time, too.
So, on math, losing my mind. I was so
horny in the sixth grade.
I couldn't even get through science
textbooks, you know? I remember there
were like diagrams of like, you know,
remember the lady where like they show
her organs and her stomach's invisible.
I ripped that out of the book and I kept
it in my closet for a while. [laughter]
For a while. And then my friend was
like, "You can see naked people on the
internet." And I was like, "I'll use
that information immediately." That's
like the most exciting thing I've ever
heard. I'm so tired of the invisible
stomach lady. [laughter]
This cartoon invisible stomach lady, she
doesn't do it for me anymore.
I've advanced past.
And so I went home. I snuck into my
father's computer room. I got completely
naked. I don't know why. [laughter]
Just how I was doing it back then. First
few years, naked every time. [laughter]
There was no rush. There was no rush in
those days. B. I had socks on,
[laughter]
socks, completely naked. I sit in the
family computer chair. This is
everybody's chair.
This isn't Michael's chair. Skinned to
leather. I don't care. And I'm on a Dell
computer. It's It's pumping hot air in
the room. I'm sweating. I'm sliding
around on the family computer chair.
It's my night, baby. [laughter]
And I didn't know what pornography was.
I just knew you could see naked people.
So, I didn't know what to look up. So, I
Googled vagina.com.
>> [laughter]
>> That's where I started. And it wasn't a
real website, but Google knew what I was
doing. [laughter]
Google was there with the assist. It was
like, "Did you mean?" And I I I did
mean. [laughter]
Didn't know how how much I meant. You
know, Google was showing me stuff. I was
like, "I didn't know I meant that, but I
[\h__\h] mean that." [laughter]
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Click, click, click.
Refresh. [laughter]
So, I'm in there. Who knows how long?
Days have gone by. I finally grew the
beard I've always wanted. [laughter]
And all of a sudden, I feel my father
behind me. You just feel him. I know. So
easy to feel your dad behind you
[laughter] when you're completely naked
watching porn on his computer basically.
[laughter]
And he's right. He's looking at my my
only my naked back. His only boy's naked
back. And as if he's James Bond, I do a
full naked Dr. Evil because I'm on a
computer chair so it swivels. [laughter]
So I go like a full naked just like
hello.
I should have had a cat, you know? It
should have been like well well
[laughter]
somebody's home sooner than I thought
they'd be.
But I wasn't a villain or cool. So all I
really did was like
[laughter]
and he made some horrible dad sound. He
was like
a piece of him died and left and it
sounded like and I killed him. I watched
him die in those eyes. I didn't even
recognize my father in those eyes. I saw
Tom for the first time. [laughter]
I saw the man my father was.
And we're just there. And I know I broke
him cuz it's like a year went by. I was
like and then he pointed at me and he
said, "Don't another." And then he ran
out of the room. [laughter]
No one's ever said don't another in the
history of the earth. [laughter] Those
words have never been next to each
other. That's a brand new thing. Brand
new thing he said. Makes no sense to say
don't to another.
But I knew what he meant because I was
like, I'm probably gonna do it another.
[laughter]
Many anothers on this. I think I'm
finally good at something. I could be
the best. But he was cool. He like uh
you know, I put all my clothes back on
and we talked. He was like, "It's
nothing to be ashamed about." I was
like, "I think it's something to be
ashamed about. [laughter]
This is it's okay to be ashamed about
this." He's like, "I'm not going to tell
anyone." Which was nice. I don't know
why the [\h__\h] you would, but
>> [laughter]
>> Thanks for not bullying me if that's
what you mean.
But I got caught cuz of the vagina.com.
I didn't know that didn't just go away
[laughter] when you typed it, you know.
So I t and I typed in a few times. I
didn't know how to spell that word.
I had some fs in there, some J's, you
know. [laughter] So my sister used a
computer. She's like, who went to four
vagina.coms
and like two fajita.coms? What's going
on [laughter]
in this home? I was like, I get horny.
[laughter]
It's the end of that story.
I uh Do you guys think the world's going
to end in our [laughter] lifetime?
>> Hell no.
>> No, it's positive. David Adenboroough.
That guy thinks the world's going to
end. Do you know the Planet Earth guy?
I'm David Adenboro. That guy [laughter]
you like do drugs, you turn that on
and you watch. He's so He's so He's like
I like him cuz he'll show you nature,
but he doesn't do it for free. He holds
you accountable. [laughter]
He'll be like, "This is the greatest
waterfall in all of the Amazon." And
it'll be like, "And you're ruining it,
you piece of [\h__\h] [laughter]
What the [\h__\h] wrong with you?" But if
you watch long enough, it sounds like
he's going to end the world. You know,
he's always like, "These penguins won't
make it through the winter." [laughter]
And if you pan out, he just has a sniper
rifle.
Well, my name isn't David R. Ratenboro.
[laughter]
Oh, to be the hand of God.
Smells his gun.
But it does seem bad. You know, we're
always in a drought. Every forest fire
burns more acres than I even knew
existed on the earth. [laughter] Every
forest fire is like, the fires burned 3
million acres. I'm always like, I should
be on fire right now. I didn't even know
we've had that many acres at all.
My friend has a house on two acres. It's
the biggest place in the world.
[laughter]
You tell me we don't have we got all
these acres and I'll get fired up like
we got to do something about it. We got
to change something. And then I'll drive
around and all the acres I care about
are okay. So [laughter]
I'm just like I'm hungry.
All right. My name's Michael Lancella.
Thank you guys so much. [cheering]
[applause]
I'm in a good mood, dude. I was in a bad
mood earlier. I was in a bad day. I post
a clip on Instagram. We all got to do
that all the time as comedians. It kind
of sucks. And I don't usually read my
comments, but this was going kind of
viral. I was like, "Oh, I'm gonna treat
myself to a couple comments." And the
first comment I read said, "Look at this
Count Choula looking bitch." And
[laughter]
that hadund Did you say I could see it,
you piece of [\h__\h]
[laughter]
That makes sense. That comment had 148
likes on it and two of them were my
friends. So,
[laughter]
this is good. That's so funny, dude. I
could see it. I I just realized we're
filming this. There's going to be a
million com I see you, too. Um
[laughter]
Oh, this is good, man. I'm happy. I got
married this past year myself. Pretty
exciting. Hey, [cheering] thanks, dude.
[applause] I think I'm at a good age to
be married. I'm 35. I think that's a
good age to get married. You know, I got
engaged the first time when I was 21 cuz
I'm from Indiana and they make you do
that. And uh it didn't work out. She
ended up cheating on me while we lived
together, which was a bummer. But it did
give me the opportunity to pack angrily,
which was kind of fun. You ever pack
angrily? It's not your best packing job.
You know, I was unpacking like, "Oh, I
took the oven knobs. That was a weird
move." All right. Well, good to have
backups. Those are going bad all the
time. [laughter]
The only thing that was messed up about
it really, the only thing that lingers,
she cheated on me with a doctor. And
that's [\h__\h] up to do to somebody,
dude. Cuz now I don't trust doctors,
dog. I don't go to the doctor ever.
Ever. If there's any doctors in here,
[\h__\h] you. Also, [laughter]
also, if you could look at some [\h__\h] for
me after the show, that would be sick as
hell. That would be really cool. No, I
don't trust doctors, dude. You go to the
doctor and they always pull that [\h__\h]
They're like, "Hey, turn your head and
cough." And you're like, "Why?" Nice.
You can [\h__\h] my wife while looking that
way. You piece of [\h__\h] [laughter] I
know your games.
>> That was a [laughter] dumb one. All
right.
No, I do think 35 is a good age to get
married, dude. Cuz now I'm not insecure
about [\h__\h] I don't get jealous of her
or any of that stuff. I know that for
sure because me when me and my wife
moved in together, she moved in a bunch
of her ex-boyfriend's t-shirts and
hoodies and [\h__\h] that she had collected
over the years. Yeah. I think as a
younger man that might have made me feel
kind of weird, but now I wear his [\h__\h]
to go to sleep. I don't care. [\h__\h] it.
[laughter] Free clothes, [\h__\h]
He was bigger than me, too, so I feel
safe at night when I put them on. Pretty
cool. I walk around the house in his
clothes all day. I'm just like, "Oh, I'm
Derek. I'm a big man. Oh, I'll protect
us.
Oh, I'm Derek. I could muster up an
erection whenever I feel like.
[laughter]
Oh, I'm Derek. I'd never call it
mustering up an erection. [laughter]
Don't get the wrong idea. That's a joke.
I'll get hard right now. [laughter]
No, I'll do it later. Um,
no. I uh I do like being married. I
think uh I don't know. I've learned some
stuff being married. I learned I know
way less about my male friends than my
wife knows about her girlfriends. Do you
guys feel like that's generally true?
Male friendship is kind of [\h__\h] dumb,
you know? She'll ask me how I know how I
know one of my good buddies. I'm just
like, he likes beer. He's a good guy.
You know, it's like kindergarten
friendship, you know? I'm like, we both
like the color blue. Don't worry about
us. We got a lot to talk about,
actually. [laughter]
But we were sending out our wedding
invitations and she was like, who do you
want to invite? And I was like, well, we
got to invite my buddy Scuzz. [laughter]
She was like, well, do you know Scuzz's
last name? And I was like, honey, I
don't know Scuz's first name. We just
got to
>> [laughter]
>> Hope for the best.
It's true. Men don't go that deep ever.
We're just not that close, you know?
Like women go way deep. If I'm hanging
out with one of my guys, we just talk
about sports and [\h__\h] If I hang out
with one of my girlfriends, we're having
a couple drinks. We we get we get deep
fast. Like I was hanging out with my
friend Lauren a few weeks ago and we
were having a couple cocktails and she
said this thing. We're talking about our
childhoods and she goes, "You know, if I
could go back in time, I'd give little
girl me a big hug." which is very sweet,
but what a waste of a time machine,
right? Like [laughter] that's what
you're going to do. You're not going to
go back and kill Hitler or put Mark
Wahberg on one of those 9/11 planes.
That's what I would do.
[laughter] He said he WOULD FIX IT, SIR.
I WANT TO SEE THAT. That sounds cool as
hell [laughter] if it works out. If not,
two less Ted movies. Sorry, [\h__\h] Oh,
you guys love Ted. [\h__\h] you. [laughter]
I don't know who that was. I'm going to
be honest. I love Ted as well. No, I'll
tell you what I wouldn't do with a time
machine. I wouldn't go back and try to
give little boy me a big hug. I don't
think that would work. I don't think
that would work for most guys. Like
right now, picture me, beer in hand, and
I just go, you know, I go back in time
and I find little 8-year-old me coming
out of school and I'm just like, "HEY
THERE, FELLA. WHAT'S GOING ON? GET OVER
HERE, YOU LITTLE BASTARD." You know,
he'd be like, "Who the [\h__\h] are you?"
I'll be like, "No, no, no. I just want
one hug and I'll get the hell out of
here." That's [laughter] it. One big hug
and I'm gone. We both need this.
[laughter]
Just go to jail in the past. That's no
good.
My wife wants to have kids pretty soon,
actually. That kind of scares me, you
know, cuz I didn't have a I didn't have
a dad growing up, and I want to be a
good dad. I will say that. I want to be
a good dad, but I'm not sure I didn't
have a good dad as a role model. I will
say I don't think you need a dad as much
as you used to. You know, you need a
good mom for sure for like love and
stuff, but like dads are supposed to
teach. Moms are way more important,
dude. They are. Cuz if you have a bad
dad, you become like a comedian or like
or like one of the greatest athletes of
all time, you know? But you don't have a
good mom, you become a serial killer,
you know? You need a good mom cuz dads
are supposed to teach you [\h__\h] you
know? I didn't have that growing up. And
I had to learn how to tie a tie recently
cuz nobody ever taught me. And then I
found this old guy on YouTube and he
taught me and now he's my dad. You can
just pick a dad, dude. They're all over
the internet. Just pick a guy [laughter]
and write I love you daddy on his
videos. So if he doesn't block you,
that's your dad. [laughter]
Congratulations to you. You are a
35year-old man with a new papa.
I love old dudes on YouTube, too, cuz
they don't waste any time. You follow
younger YouTubers, you got to skip the
first four minutes of their videos
because they all think they're going to
be influencers. So, the first four
minutes is always like, "Hey, before we
get to the whole point of the video,
don't forget TO SMASH THAT LIKE AND
SUBSCRIBE. DON'T FORGET TO HIT FOLLOW
AND hit the alarm button for alerts."
This old dude I follow doesn't do any of
that [\h__\h] HE'S JUST LIKE, "HERE'S HOW
YOU DO IT." ALL RIGHT. THERE'S NO TIME.
[laughter]
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME. GODAMN IT.
And don't follow me. WHAT ARE YOU GAY?
[laughter]
He's oldfashioned. I don't like that he
talks like that, but he's my dad. He's a
good guy. [laughter]
And he doesn't know how to edit either.
All of his videos are one shot, dude.
They're one and done. There's no cuts.
There's no zooms. And I was watching him
grill the other day. He teach me how to
grill a steak. He's a good dad. And uh
[laughter]
after like 4 minutes, he just goes, "I
have to go to the bathroom now." And
then he just walked off screen. And I
just watched a hot grill for a while.
[laughter]
Hope dad comes back. Hope he's not like
the others.
[laughter]
Drinking a little beer. I hope that's
cool. [laughter] I've been drinking a
lot lately, dude. I've been drinking a
lot of Bud Light, brother. I've been I'm
fixing it, dude. I'm [laughter] I'm
saving their brand. I I'm They're going
to have a good quarter cuz of me. You
guys know what happened with Bud Light?
They got cancelled by the right because
a transgender person drank Bud Light on
their Instagram and that pissed a bunch
of people off. It was sponsored content
and Kid Rock shot a machine gun
[laughter] at a bunch of Bud Lights,
which was a good point,
but it made it to where now is a great
time. If you're an alcoholic, it's a
good time to get into Bud Light. Cuz now
I could drink like 20 Bud Lights on my
couch and if my wife is like, "What the
[\h__\h] are you doing?" I could be like,
"Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't know I was
married to a goddamn bigot." Okay.
[laughter]
I didn't KNOW I MARRIED JK [\h__\h]
ROWLING. ALL RIGHT.
BY THE WAY, THE JK Rowling [\h__\h] is
hilarious, too. Do you guys know about
JK Rowling? She said a bunch of
anti-transgender [\h__\h] and it made it to
where now if you're super anti-woke
online, you also have to be super pro-H
Harry Potter, which [laughter] is that's
just a good time, man. That's very
funny. If you're on like Twitter or X or
whatever you want to call it, and you
say something anti-Hary Potter, you'll
get a flood of these dudes with American
flags in their profile that are just
like, I'd like to see this. Soy boy
train a hippogri.
[laughter]
I'd like to see this libard dodge a
quaffle, you know. [laughter]
Pretty good. I don't know.
Sorry. I know. We're in a we're in a fun
time. We're in my favorite time of uh
we're we're leading into election
season. That's like my favorite time
because we're about to meet my favorite
people, which are undecided voters.
Undecided voters are the funniest
[\h__\h] people in the world to me. It's
not like if you don't agree with
somebody that's fine. But not having any
idea is so [\h__\h] funny. JUST LIKE I
GOT NOTHING.
YOU GO INTO THE BOOTH like who knows
what's GOING TO HAPPEN IN THERE.
[laughter]
And it's always the same dude. It's a
guy who's like I don't like either
candidate. You know just once I wish it
was a guy who was like I don't know who
to VOTE FOR. I LOVE BOTH THESE GUYS.
[laughter]
It's going to be a HELL OF A FOUR YEARS
EITHER WAY.
ALSO, it's like that time where they're
trying to like raise money for their
campaigns and [\h__\h] The politician I
[\h__\h] up. I gave Biden the money last
last time and I'm I'm I'll never do that
again cuz it was a Here's the thing. I
got I got roped in, dog. Cuz they all
posted Biden posted this thing on
Instagram where he was like, "Look, man.
If I don't get like 20 bucks right now,
it's all over for me, man. [laughter] I
just need like 20 bucks and it'll be
I'll be straight." All right.
I gave it to him. I was like, "Shit, I
feel bad for this guy." So, I gave it to
him, you know, and then I regretted it
immediately cuz I started getting these
emails every day from Joe Biden.
[laughter]
It would say from Joe Biden to Tom and
it would say, "Hey Tom, I'm scared." I
[laughter] was LIKE, "WHAT? YOU CAN'T
TALK TO ME LIKE THAT. YOU'RE THE GUY.
TOM, THINGS ARE looking pretty dire,
man." [laughter]
He was asking me for money every day. He
sounded like a crack. He was like, "If I
can just get like 38 cents, man.
>> [laughter]
>> I get a bus ticket to Washington. I'll
go fix this [\h__\h] I will.
[laughter]
I'll suck your dick, Tom. Is that what
you need? I'm just so sad. [laughter]
No, but I am 35, which means technically
I'm old enough to be president now. And
I got some big ideas for this country,
brother. I do. I got some big Here's my
first big idea. I think this is actually
fix some [\h__\h] I think we should have a
tax for hot people. I do. I think if
you're super hot, you should have to pay
an extra tax because nobody would be mad
about that. Not really. If you got a
letter in the mail [laughter] that was
like, "You have to pay the hot people
tax."
You'd be like, "Oh, [\h__\h] yeah.
[laughter]
About time.
About time the government saw what I've
been doing out here.
Been busting my ass. [laughter]
You could write off your ugly family."
How mad would you be if you got that tax
one year and didn't get it the next? You
know, you'd be calling up the government
like, "I think there's been a mistake
and they'd be like, "No, you let
yourself go this year, Britney. You got
to step it up, sister. Come on."
[laughter]
I think hot people tax. I also think big
dick tax. That's right. You got a big
old dick on, you got to pay up, [\h__\h]
[laughter] You got a big old crank
hanging out there, YOU GOT TO PAY.
[laughter]
I'm not even a comedian. I just wander
into surf shops. ANYBODY BACK HERE GOT A
BIG DICK? HUH? [screaming] COME ON. GIVE
ME A COUPLE BUCKS.
IT'S ONLY FAIR. FAIR is fair. [laughter]
I do think it would be good. I think
some guys with big dicks might like
that. You know, there's guys who have
big old hogs on heard of these guys. Got
big old cranks for But that doesn't mean
people see them all the time. Some guys
got sneaky big dicks, you know, cuz you
might have a big old dick but got a bad
personality or a weird tooth or an ugly
face or no good stories from the sea or
whatever women are attracted to these
days. So, nobody ever sees it. It's just
a big dick blowing in the wind. into
what a tragedy, you know, cuz you can't
run around being like, "Hey, I got a big
one. I'll show it TO YOU RIGHT NOW. YOU
hop out of a bush. Come on. It's right
here." You know, that's not attractive.
But now you wouldn't have to do that.
Now you could just be like, "Hey,
taxes were pretty bad this year, huh?
[laughter]
Let's just say your boy had to fill out
a W9 and a half. Is that good?"
[laughter]
All right. You guys have been [\h__\h]
awesome. I'm topic. Thank you.
[cheering]
[applause]
>> You guys ready to die? Just kidding.
What's up? [laughter] What's up?
Would you be upset if I killed you?
[laughter]
One of you? I don't think so. Do you
have a gun? Who's got a gun?
[laughter]
Nobody. I wanted a gun for a little bit.
I wanted a gun. I'm so afraid of getting
like my apartment broken into. But then
I was and I was going to get one. Then I
was like, I'm also afraid I'm going to
kill myself. So, you have to like
[laughter]
weigh out the options, you know what I
mean? I sat down with a little pros and
cons thing, you know? I was like, how
often does a breaking and entering
really happen? Never, right? But, you
know, every day I'm like, I want to
[\h__\h] die. Kill me. You know,
[laughter]
LIKE, SOMEONE KILL ME. [screaming]
THAT'S EVERY DAY. Every night.
No gun for me. Remember when they wanted
to give teachers guns? That could have
been my gun.
If I was a teacher, I'd love to have a
gun.
[laughter] That's how I would introduce
myself. First day, September, I'd go,
"Hello, class. My name is
Mr. Sagalot."
[laughter]
[laughter] Right.
Also want to I don't know. There's too
many people walking up to us like, you
know, getting in our like putting us on
their [\h__\h] YouTube and [\h__\h] That
would be nice to have a gun for that.
Some guy going up, what do you do for a
living? Oh, this you [\h__\h] idiot.
Guess what? This is what I do.
I'm so You know what? I've been on
TikTok. I just I'm on TikTok all day or
like reals or whatever. All day I'm just
swiping and I'm like I'm watching these
teenagers prank people and it's getting
me livid.
I hate them. [clears throat] I hate
people pranking people. I'm so afraid
it's going to happen to me. Like a guy
fell down in front of me the other day
and I thought he was trying to Tik Tok
prank me. So, I didn't pick him up. I
didn't help him. He fell down in front
of me and I thought some other kid was
just filming me. And I thought if I
picked him up, he was going to go, "Can
I get a
World Star the next day? Fat lesbian has
a panic attack." [laughter]
>> [laughter]
>> Isn't that a relatable fear that you're
going to get me'd
and you're you can't get a job or [\h__\h]
for the rest of your [\h__\h] life
because you're a [\h__\h] meme?
[laughter]
I'm so memeable, too. So memeable. I get
like, you know, I got into an argument a
couple months ago and uh like we were
going to fight kind of thing. And I'm
not a fighter. Look at me. I look like a
Renaissance paintings depiction of a
queen. Okay. I don't look like a
fighter.
And uh I was losing weight at the time
and he did not think so.
[laughter]
Sincerely, if you think you're losing
weight, if you're like, "I'm on a diet.
Go pick a fight with a stranger and just
see how fat you still are." He He walked
right over. He goes, "You fat fuck." And
then I said to him, "Not as much as I
used to be. That's a true story.
[laughter]
That's a true story." And then he
laughed in my face and he was a Spanish
guy. and he went ja ja which I thought
was [laughter]
anyway. [laughter]
Whatever. Who cares? I like being right
by a window. I can just if this isn't
going well, I can just [\h__\h] jump
right out. Too many suicide jokes. Okay.
[laughter]
Oh my god. Are you guys couples? You
guys together? Hand on knee. It's cute.
We're a couple and on.
How many couples fought today and you're
like argued and you're sitting here
right now? My god, that makes me laugh
all the time picturing how many like you
have to. How many couples like before
they walked into a comedy club were
like, can we just have a good time
tonight? [laughter]
And now you're sitting here faking it.
Ha [screaming]
haha.
I love that.
Couples that go out and fight. Don't you
love seeing that [\h__\h] I was thinking
about it. There must have been a couple
that fought on the Titanic.
[laughter]
Horrible life, those people. Just
fighting with your wife on the Titanic
and then you die. Could you imagine?
Some wife is like, "The boat is
sinking." And some idiot husband's like,
"Then why is the band still playing?"
Okay,
[laughter]
I'm not falling for your boat prank.
I'm going to gamble.
I just want to have a good time.
[laughter]
Yeah, I used to fight in relationships a
lot. Me and my I have an ex
[laughter]
ladies.
I have a We used to fight all the time.
We were two different people, you know
what I mean? She was like she was very
liberal. She was democratic, you know,
she would like vote and like, you know,
she was like all that good [\h__\h] And I'm
like a fun guy. And those two things are
always going to kind of like, you know,
they're always going to bump heads. You
know what I mean? I'll give you [\h__\h]
liberal queers a little bit more of an
example. [laughter]
YOU DON'T OWN A GUN. [laughter]
YOU DON'T THINK THAT JOKE WAS FUNNY.
WHAT the hell is wrong with you? Yes.
No, I'll give you an example cuz uh this
is cuz I'm I'm left I'm liberal, too.
But I was like, you know, I don't like
telling people how to live their life.
And I Okay, here's the example. I wanted
to play the Harry Potter Hogwarts Legacy
video game. [laughter]
And she thought that made me anti-trans,
and I'm not. I don't care. I don't care
whatever you do. You know what makes me
laugh? Every time you hear someone go, I
don't feel safe with transgender women
in our public bathrooms. Does that make
you laugh? Has anybody here been in a
public bathroom and felt safe?
>> [laughter]
>> Have you WALKED INTO A PUBLIC? OH, SAFE,
SAFETY, SAFE. I'm so safe here.
[laughter]
Look at it. This guy's sleeping. That's
how safe he is.
This guy, I DON'T EVEN THINK HE'S
BREATHING. HE'S SO CALM. [laughter]
And also, not for nothing, if you do
feel so unsafe in a public bathroom,
don't you want a muscular woman in
there? [laughter]
You know, don't you want a woman who
could tuck her balls behind her back and
be like, "Go piss. I'll watch the door.
You go piss. [laughter]
Anybody comes in here, I'll [\h__\h] them in
the ass.
Dry style.
>> Oh.
[laughter]
Oh,
you guys go to therapy. [laughter]
I'm in therapy. My therapist is such an
[\h__\h]
Either day. He goes, he goes,
not the other day. Oh, comics all the
time or like the other day. This was 6
years ago. Six years ago. [laughter] 6
years ago. He goes, he goes, "What you
got to do, Brendon, is you got to stop
smoking weed and you got to stop jerking
off all the time." And that I never went
to him with jerking off is a problem
that I have. [laughter]
You just put that Can they put stuff on
you? He's like, "By buddy, the minute I
shook your hand, I knew."
And now when I jerk off, I think about
him, which is a [\h__\h] problem. But
what are you going to do? You know,
you guys get into arguments with people.
Someone's just trying to test your
gangster. Anybody? [laughter]
You know what I'm talking about.
Just get into a [\h__\h] argument with
someone on the street. [\h__\h] you.
I got into an argument with a guy and uh
this is the last argument I got into.
We're going back and forth. We're doing
our [\h__\h] [\h__\h] you. [\h__\h] you. And then at
the end of the argument, he blew a kiss
at me.
[laughter] He was like, "All right,
buddy."
And I caught the kiss instinctually.
[laughter]
Cut that out, please. Can Can YOU CAN WE
CUT THAT ONE OUT? [laughter]
They're not Can you monetize on this set
at all?
[laughter]
>> You guys smoke weed?
>> Yeah. Yeah, [laughter] one guy. Yes. Oh,
I love it. I love smoking weed. It's
It's [\h__\h] sick. I like going places
high. I'm like I like getting high
everywhere, you know? I I would visit my
grandma. High. That was awesome.
Sick. Do that. Do it. It's perfect. My
grandma had dementia. I'm high. So,
we're both just standing there like,
[laughter]
"Oh, what's our names again?
All right, I gotta go. But [laughter]
okay, but this is fun, you know? It's
fun doing standup. It's always fun doing
standup and whatever the hell this is
[laughter]
with this [\h__\h] guy looking at me the
entire time. I I've done a lot of crazy
gigs. I did it again at Riker's Island.
You know what that is?
>> It's prison. I paid my nickel. I paid I
did my time. They call you too and they
come up on your caller ID as jail. like
prison. [laughter] There's no like
unknown caller. It's like Riker's Island
calling. And I'm not [\h__\h] around. I
just did not go to jury duty that week.
Like I did not show up. [laughter]
Just missed it. I missed jury duty. And
then jails calling.
I literally was like, "Oh my god,
they're so quick."
Like, "Is this how they arrest white
people?" Speaking.
[laughter]
This is he.
This is E.
And I did the gig, which was a
nightmare, as you can imagine. And the
guy when he booked us, he goes, "Oh, by
the way, you're uh you're about to
perform for the Latin Kings of Riker's
Island." And I had I just had like a
[\h__\h] fit. I don't know why. I had a
little stick up my ass or something. And
I went, "Hey, man. You got to tell us
that before we agree to the gig, okay?"
And he goes, "Why?
>> [laughter]
>> And then I go I go, "Well, you don't
know. I could be an enemy of the Latin
Kings." I said that to him and he
literally was like, "I think you're
good." [laughter]
He was like, "Unless the Latin Kings are
beefing with the Macy's Rewards cards
members." [laughter]
All right, you guys have been great,
man. Thank you very much. Have
[cheering] a good one. [applause]
>> This is insane. Um, everyone here is is
so young and hot and it's just nice to
fit in somewhere somewhere. [laughter]
We all look rich and that's where we
differ. Uh, [laughter]
I don't know. I've had a lot of life
decisions that led me to this point and
I just I do shows every night and after
every show I go and I sit in my car and
I pull down that little mirror and I
look at myself in the mirror and I say,
"Kather, you're so cute. [laughter]
You could have SOLD MEDICAL EQUIPMENT.
>> [laughter]
>> I DON'T I DON'T KNOW WHERE IT WENT
WRONG. I think so hot. And I can't
distractingly hot. So, if you can move.
Um
[laughter]
I I I grew up a horse girl. We got any
other white freaks in here? OF COURSE
YOU ARE. Cuz you are. You're like,
"Yeah, I was a horse girl and then I
grew into a horse lady and just I'm a
palamino." Cool. Okay. beautiful
[laughter] horseair. Cool. And then your
your stallion over here. Thank you so
much for rubbing that in my face. Uh did
you ride here? Did [laughter]
you look at you eating your little oats
over there? Shut up. [laughter]
Shut up. Get in your [\h__\h] stable
right now,
you hot [\h__\h] And [laughter]
I I was a horse girl. I was obsessed
with horses growing up, but my parents,
they didn't want to get me a horse. uh
or they didn't want to pay for horseback
riding lessons. So me and my friends, we
were just horses for each other.
[laughter] You remember these horse
girls? You remember these girls? Oh, the
recess bell would ring and they
got in their way. They [snorts] let you
know, right?
[laughter]
Dude, we we took horse real seriously.
We only had to put down one girl.
[laughter]
And I got sent to the principal for
that. [laughter]
What? And the principal was like, "Now,
why does Kelly keep saying you
euthanized her?" [laughter]
I was like, "Well, first of all, her
name is Lightning Bolt.
Respect the fallen." [laughter]
And you know what happened? She was the
first to start her period. So, she
swelled up to double D's.
and she couldn't gallop anymore.
[laughter]
That and my crush had a crush on her cuz
you know she just she had that strong
chest. She was the Clydesdale.
[laughter]
You remember your high school boyfriend.
Uh [laughter]
this is that was my life growing up. I
we Oh, okay. We would have middle school
mixers. I was in middle school, too. I'm
not a pervert. [laughter]
I remember my first middle school mixer.
I showed up and all the other girls
showed up and you know they had their
abberro and fitch spring collection on.
You know what I mean? They look they had
that little moose right here on their
shirt, right? [laughter]
And I showed up in my dress barn
juniors. You know, I had a I had a
little squirrel right here. [laughter]
My shirt. Sometimes we got lucky. My mom
would dress as an American Eagle
knockoff. That was dope cuz we we it'd
be a little eagle right here, right?
With a with a little squirrel and its
talons right here. [laughter]
And I remember my first mixer, all the
girls gathered in in the gymnasium and
they started playing Little John and all
the girls started twerking, right? But
it was real stiff. We were white
Catholics. [laughter]
You know, you've seen a litter of scared
puppies before.
[laughter]
It was my first time seeing what
twerking was. I'd never seen it. The
only other dance I've been to before
that was a fatherdaughter dance and
[laughter]
they didn't have that there.
[laughter] So I was watching them and as
I was watching them, you know, the boys
would come up behind them and they do
that night dance and I'm learning this
and as I'm watching them that
[clears throat] this boy comes up behind
me, this little bottom feeder comes up.
[laughter]
looking for the night dance, right? I
was like, "Okay, I'm going to try this,
but I'm I'm real white." Okay, a beat is
just a vegetable to me. [laughter]
So, I was like, "All right." So, I what
I did, I just I just danced out the
actual words of the song, you know? I
was just like, "Okay, to the window."
And I just did A LITTLE SQUARE TO THE
WALL. I GOT REAL STAM [laughter]
ALL THAT SWEAT DROPPED DOWN, YOU I JUST
did a sad W BALLS [screaming]
and the whole time that boy's pelvis
just had a hard time [laughter]
guessing where I was headed to next
till eventually he had to detach. So he
could puke [laughter]
um for motion sickness.
Everybody else was grinding. I was just
doing yin gang twins pictionary.
[laughter]
Somebody one time was like, "You were
interpretive dancing." I was like, "No,
I was interruptive dancing." [laughter]
I interrupted that young man's boner.
This I I grew up Catholic. I I only date
Catholics. This is why I I was dating a
guy in college one time and he took me
to meet his older sister and I thought
she was real cool because because she
was real cool. And uh I was real new.
Like I'd never I was I was gray. I'd
never done a drug before in my life. And
we get there and she's like, "Y'all
drove a long way. You want to hit this
bowl?" I was like, "Yeah, I'm starving."
And [laughter]
I was like, "What kind of chia seeds is
this?" And she was like, "This it's
marijuana." And I was like, "Oh, man. I
wish I could, but I just did a lot of
melatonin." And [laughter]
as you can see, because my hands are
melting. Uh, and she goes, "Oh, don't
worry, girl. I got you. I'll shotgun
you." Right. And I was like, "Oh, I know
we just met, but I'm I'm good. I'm kind
of a liberal." And [laughter]
nevertheless, she persisted. And so
[laughter]
if you don't know what shotgunning is,
it's cuz you're a nerd.
[laughter]
You know, she just made the chamber with
her hands, right? My mouth on one end,
her mouth on the other. And then she she
took she took a sip right from the
devil's teeth, right?
>> [laughter]
>> And then into my mouth, she just blew.
Just just a gust of witchcraft. And
[laughter] I passed out. And a lot of
people say when they thought they died,
they they saw the light. I didn't I
didn't see the light, but I thought I
died cuz I I woke up in the Catholic
church that I'd grown up in. I was
wearing my like Catholic school uniform,
the dirty part.
[laughter]
And the only other person in the church
was Jesus. And I knew that he just seen
me doing drugs cuz he was looking at me
so disappointed. Yeah, he was just like,
[laughter]
[laughter] you know, he just threw his
arms out, you know. She just like, "Oh,
oh man." You know, sorry. Oh, man. Yeah.
[laughter] And before I could ask for
forgiveness, I really woke up cuz his
sister had splashed me in the face with
their red wine and I was like, "Oh, I've
been saved by the blood of Christ."
[laughter]
She's like, "No, it's Pino Noir from
Kroger. WE'RE JEWISH, [\h__\h]
DO I HAVE KROGER OUT HERE? [laughter]
NO. NO. Y'all don't know what I'm
talking about. Cool. Well, it's the poor
uh grocery store. [laughter]
I'm from the south. My parents are
cousins. And
that actually is true. [laughter]
I took one of those dads. I was like,
"Dad, why is why is mom's cousin on your
side?" And he's like, "Eat your
meatloaf." And [laughter]
this is true. Um, I did find that out.
This is Well, I was upset when I found
out. I should tell you that. And this is
I wasn't mad that it happened. I do not
blame my parents. They were very young
when they met. It was puppy love. Same
litter.
[laughter]
Dude, I was just mad. I didn't find out
till I was 26 years old. I was like, I
was like, yo, I could have used this
when I was younger, you know? Imagine
the scholarships I could have gotten.
[laughter]
I didn't know I was diverse, you know?
I just wish I would have known for this
one situation like this. It was always
like remember when you go it was like
elementary school and you'd go to your
first day to class and the teacher would
be like okay guys it's our first day
let's all get to know each other right
and she'd be like go around tell us your
name and and tell us an interesting fact
you know and I've never I didn't know I
was special and [laughter] I was like oh
no we got two gerbles we can't find one
my dad has eczema you know I didn't have
[laughter]
anything cool there was always those
kids that couldn't wait to be called on
I remember one time this kid raised his
hand was like uh I'm bilingual and we
were in Kentucky so we didn't know what
that meant [laughter]
but we knew he was a spy.
[laughter]
I just wish I could have BEEN LIKE, "OH
YEAH, WELL MY cousin is me." [laughter]
[laughter] Okay. My friends and I, we're
obsessed with like the influencers, the
Instagram influencers. They'll go to
like Tulum, Mexico. Statistically, one/4
of you have been there and [laughter]
because you're young and hot.
Well, we we're obsessed with the in
Instagram influencers that they'll go to
like Tulum, Mexico, you know, and
they'll take like a yacht excursion and
they take a picture sipping a a
cocktail, right, made out of the bone
marrow of an endangered ostrich, right?
[laughter]
My friends and I, we were like, we're we
were like, we're going to go on that
trip. So, we put all of our money
together and we went to Fort Lauderdale,
Florida. [laughter] And
it was so fun. We were like, we're going
to go on a yacht excursion. So, we found
a man on Craigslist [laughter]
to take us on his pontoon. And
[laughter] he was so nice. It sound It
sounds dangerous. I know cuz But we knew
we were safe cuz his name was Salt
Daddy. So [laughter]
we were like, he has daughters
and he was great. He took us out into
the ocean. We played pretend kidnap and
[laughter]
the whole time he wore his gut
and he played his music, you know, he
poured his drinks and we did what good
little little white girls are supposed
to do. You know, we were twerking
[laughter] to Tim McGrath.
Live like you were dying.
Right. And we were feeling really sexy
cuz Salt Daddy was taking a lot of
videos [laughter] and
and then in the middle of the ocean when
we got there, he was like, "Hey, I hope
y'all don't mind some of my friends are
going to join us." And we were like,
"Oh, that's a good idea." You know, more
daddies, [laughter]
you know, cuz we didn't have cell phone
service. And [laughter] we we looked and
this huge boat pulled up and we looked
and like like we were like, "Papa," you
know? Uh, but there was no daddies on
this boat, not even an uncle. It was
just this boat like full of Miami
goddesses. You know, like you know those
women with wearing those thongs and and
it just hurts to look at. You're like,
[laughter]
is that touching your urethra? Oh my
god. Is that what women's always have to
pee? And the whole butt makes you hungry
for honey baked ham [laughter]
and saw daddy. He just got on that boat
and they just took off for a couple
hours.
>> [laughter]
>> The worst part about playing kidnap
is when your captor's like, "Yeah,
actually, you're good to go. [laughter]
I got someone else."
Yeah, I'll call the authorities for you.
[laughter] Yeah. Hi. We got a lot of
abandoned elderly miners here. He looks
at our backside. Yeah. They're very
malnourished. [laughter]
Yeah. Every time I play Tim McGraw, they
just shiver violently. I think I PLAY
FOR SO MUCH. THIS IS SO FUN. [cheering]
I LOVE YOU GUYS. HI. [applause]
>> LOOK, UM, here's the thing. Uh, I
haven't slept in like 3 days. I've had
some pretty weird thoughts.
Here they come. Uh, [laughter]
does anyone else here feel that uh we
may have normalized eating ass too
quickly?
[laughter]
>> [laughter]
>> Next joke. I uh
like it showed up and everyone was fine
with it. [laughter]
And the lack of discretion we showed
as a nation.
[clears throat and laughter]
Truly horrifying.
And look, I'm not trying to make you
feel bad if you do that.
But you should know
what you're doing [laughter]
is [\h__\h] disgusting.
My real issue with it is this. Like
look, uh the thing is like look, number
one, I know no one wants to do it to me.
And look, I don't even want it done to
me, but I do want someone to want to do
it to me.
Two, everything has been sexually
normalized now, which I think is good.
You know, you should be able to come
however you want. Uh, like within the
bounds of the law. [laughter]
I think you should be able to start
sniffing city bike seats or whatever.
But, uh,
[laughter]
just so you know, I'm going to match the
energy you're giving ME
[laughter]
and this is what you're doing.
So, we'll see if we can bring it up or
not.
>> [laughter]
>> But my real issue with it is like
see if the moment you say you're not
into some whackadoo kinky [\h__\h] people
act like you're approved all of a
sudden. He's like, "What do you mean you
don't like having your balls whipped
with a radiator?"
I had a buddy of mine say to me, he
goes, "You're not eating ass yet?" He
said it like it was kale. like I
[laughter]
like you're not eating ass yet. I was
like, "No, I'm not." And to be honest, I
was having enough trouble with the
front.
Don't think I was nailing that if I'm
being 100% honest.
Probably the only thing I've tried to
eat that I haven't finished. Uh,
next joke.
I always look like this, but uh I am
going through a breakup. Uh, she's
winning. Uh, but here's the thing.
Something you learn as you get a touch
older is uh like into your 20s like me.
Uh,
yeah. is um you learn not to expect
things of people they've never given to
you before. Like I got two brothers. I
don't have any other family. Like one
blows up trees for a living. Yeah. And
the other one uh I think he just does
push-ups in public bathrooms.
But I went through this breakup. I
wanted to talk to him and I text my baby
brother. I go, "Hey man, Alex and I
split up." And then he just sent back a
meme
and it was a picture of a pitbull and
all it said was bring me Fouchy.
[laughter]
There's no answer for that. Like like
how all context has been removed so
there is no response. Like that's like
if I was like what's your shoe size and
you were like the moon goes away during
the daytime. Like
[laughter]
And then like
look, I don't mind being single, but I
[\h__\h] hate dating. Uh cuz I never been
the kind of dude who would just walk up
to a woman in a bar and start hitting on
them like a [\h__\h] stranger. What are
you nuts? That's crazy. Just walk up to
someone and be like,
"Hi, [laughter]
I'm here to try and [\h__\h] you."
>> [cheering and applause]
>> It's nuts. Like they're saying
everything but the thing you know they
want to do [cheering]
and I I so I don't do that. And so I'm
on the apps and uh I'm on all of them.
Uh your boy here's got to cast a wide
net. Uh [laughter]
I'm not catching a fish with just a
spear. Uh
in fact, I might need to do the kind of
fishing that's bad for the environment.
Uh, [laughter]
drag the ocean floor and bring me my
queen.
May she be covered in kelp. Uh,
but the thing is, uh, I don't like the
apps. I think they're kind of a
tremendous time suck. Uh, so my approach
is very copy paste. So it's the same
pictures and the same answers for
everything on every app, right? And that
works fine until you realize certain
apps are for certain kinds of people.
Like Hinge is for the mentally unstable.
Uh Bumble is for beekeepers.
[laughter]
And uh I accidentally fell into Field.
I'm not sure if y'all are familiar with
Field. Well, it's a it's a real [\h__\h]
forward kind of app. Uh, it's
disgusting. [laughter] Truly, it's
nothing but abbreviations. I don't quite
understand
and graphic photos. It's just like, I'm
LGA if you're DTF. It's like, I'm
reading airport codes. What's going on
in this [\h__\h] place?
But here's where the copy paste thing
gets you in a touch of trouble. So,
like, I'm I'm funny. I think we all have
realized. Uh
but uh well uh I'm a hilarious alpha. Uh
I um
the thing is I try I go for funny like
cuz I think people see my face and
they're like, "Well, he better have a
personality." Uh so I like on the
prompts on the apps, you know, they'll
always write some [\h__\h] like, you know,
like uh tell me an interesting fact I
might not know. And then I'll write
something like, "Did you know if you
fart with your headphones in, no one can
hear it,
you know?"
Yeah. And that gets it like a little
tehe on a regular app, but on an applike
field,
[laughter]
it opens up a Pandora's box
that there is no solution for. Just
like, "Get over here and [\h__\h] my face
with your ass." And you're like, "Ah."
And I'm thinking about it. I uh
you guys were really sweet. Thanks for
letting me hang out and do that. Take
care of yourself. Thank you very much.
Enjoy yourself. [applause]
I am a woman. I'm a woman. Give it up
for me. I'm a woman. I'm doing my best
out here. [cheering] Thank you. I'm
awake. I'm trying. I'm doing my best.
I'm I don't have any kids, but I'm an
auntie, and I love it. I actually love
it. I have an eight-year-old nephew. I
love him so much. She's so adorable and
he looks at me like I'm this wise adult
with all these answers. He's very
curious. So, he's always like following
me around and asking me questions. He's
so cute. He's like, "Why is your voice
so deep, Uncle Leslie?" [laughter]
And then he goes, "Are you Mexican?" I'm
like, "What the?" [laughter]
You show some respect to your Theo.
Okay,
that's Theo Lesley to you. Okay.
All right. Where are my white people at?
Make some noise, white people. Don't be
ashamed. It's Yeah. Put your hand up.
Yeah. It's your Be a proud That's my
proud boy right there. [laughter]
Don't be ashamed. It's your year. You
deserve it. I don't know what he I don't
know what he deserved. You did it. You
You're
um I love white people. I was raised in
Orange County, so I feel so safe around
a group of white people. I love white
people.
Love white people. But it was hard
growing up in Orange County because, you
know, I was a minority. You know, I was
the only Mexican kid. It was [laughter]
hard.
It was hard to fit in. You know, I
wanted to fit in so badly. I tried so
hard to be white. Like, do you know how
many bonfires I've been to [laughter]
in my life? Just decked out head to toe,
bibong, ruka, rainbow sandals.
[laughter]
He's always blasting, counting crows
like la. Yeah. [laughter]
Just trying to impress you people. Okay.
And now looking back, I feel bad because
that was cultural appropriation what
[laughter] I was doing.
And I apologize. I'm sorry
I for disrespecting your beautiful
Caucasian culture. I [laughter]
I should have been cancelled. I went to
school and called everyone gnarly with a
hard R. [laughter]
I'm sorry. Okay.
Yeah. I love Orange County, but it's a
weird place. We went through this weird
like punk rock emo the Hot Topic phase.
The emo thing. Everyone had side bangs
for two years. It was It was weird. But
like I I never understood it. I grew up
in a nice neighborhood in Orange County,
so I'd always see a car full of bros
driving around and blasting, "Cut my
life into pieces. This is my last
resort." I'm like, they're all just like
sipping on a Jamba Juice [laughter]
and pulling into a gated community. I'm
like, "Relax, Brendan. You're going to
be [laughter]
What are you sad? You're drinking
arasmataz on a sunny day. You're going
to be fine, friend. It's going to be
you're going to be okay, dude.
[laughter]
But I escaped Orange County in my 20s. I
moved to LA. I was single for most of my
20s and I I hooked up with everybody. I
[laughter] I crushed it in my 20s. I
did. [cheering] I put up solid numbers
on the board in my 20s because if you're
a single woman in your 20s, it's very
easy. Me men M men are just available.
They're everywhere. They're very easy to
access, you know, like it was hard for
me to turn down all the men. Okay. It
just feels like, you know, when there's
a plate of fries on the table and you
eat them even if you're not hungry, you
know? I was like, "Someone take these
dicks away from me." Like, I'm
[laughter]
I'm stuffed. I'm stuffed. I'm not even
hungry. Take them away. I'm not even
hungry. Stop. [laughter] But you'll if
you'll have one, I'll have one. You know
what I mean? It's
the weekend. Let's be bad. It's the
weekend. [laughter]
But I'm single still in my 30s. And it's
hard in my 30s because I have to prepare
for my future even though I'm single.
Like I froze my eggs last year. I don't
know if anyone's done it. Women my age,
we have to think about this now. And if
you've It's miserable. It's painful. You
give yourself shots every day. It's so
expensive. And I did this entire
procedure and I don't even know if I
want kids.
And I don't even know if my husband
wants kids. [laughter]
And I don't even know who he is.
Who am I doing this for? Who is this
useless man I'm supposed to marry? I
haven't even met this guy yet and I'm
mad at him. [laughter]
It's never going to work. Okay,
I'm 36 and I've never been married. So,
I've never met the one or whatever, you
know, but I even though I've never met
this guy, I think about him. I wonder
about him, you know, like what does he
like? Where does he live? What does he
do? You know, I'm thinking he's got to
be pretty special, right? But I don't
think we should hype up our soulmates
this much cuz I've been waiting my
entire life to meet this one man.
And I'm I'm not trying to sound mean,
but I know he's not going to be worth
the wait. [laughter]
You know, I'm sure he's a nice guy. You
know what I mean? But it's like it's
just going to be some guy named Greg in
a graphic tea.
If someone if someone pointed at Greg
and said, "Leslie, you get to marry this
man, but you have to wait
[laughter] 36 years,
I wouldn't even get in line." [laughter]
Okay? Do you understand?
I'd wait half an hour tops for someone
like Greg. [laughter]
I do want to get married though. I have
I I can't believe I want to get married
still cuz I I see you married people and
you guys don't look like you're having a
lot of fun. Okay. [laughter] What do
people always describe marriage as? It's
always work, compromise, sacrifice, you
know, like are you in love? Are you
training for the Olympics? Like why are
you so sweaty? [laughter]
It's so like every time I I ask my
married friends like, "Yeah, how's it
going? How's married life?" That you
guys are so dejected. You know, you guys
always look like the losing coach in a
postgame interview.
[laughter]
Uh yeah. Uh [laughter]
this is not the outcome that we had
hoped for.
But I believe in my team, you know. It's
like why are you guys [laughter]
so sad?
Very, very sad.
I don't know. It's not it's not easy
being a straight woman. It's actually I
I rarely meet someone that gets me
smitten. You know, being straight, it's
actually a struggle for me because I I'm
attracted to men, but I don't find men
attractive. [laughter]
The women always seem to laugh really
hard. Do you know what [laughter] I
mean?
It's like, I want you to hold me, but do
you always have to wear a hat?
[laughter]
Is that how you guys get ready? Look how
good she looks. And that's how you get
Can you guys just try? Can you guys just
try a little bit to get ready for us?
[laughter]
I can't believe I'm I can't believe I'm
straight. I can't believe it. Cuz I
Women are beautiful. Any woman will walk
by and she could change your life. But
I've never seen some floating hat in a
crowd. [laughter]
Who is that man? [laughter]
Right there in those Costco basketball
shorts. Oh my god,
you guys are the worst.
>> I don't know. I'll find someone fun. I
I'm I like to have I like to party
still. Like I love music festivals. Love
house music. I love that stuff. I just
don't know why the most successful DJs
are men. It doesn't make sense to me
because in real life, the best DJs are
clearly straight women,
okay? Cuz we're out here remixing men
all the time, right? Every time we break
up with a man and send him off to his
next relationship,
we're like, remix.
It's Jason with career ambition.
Like, oh, here we go. It's Anthony, but
he's a better communicator.
Another one. [laughter]
It's Michael, but with clean towels.
Like, [laughter]
you guys don't even know. Like, this is
how women support women. We just go
around fixing each other's future
husbands under the table. No commission.
[laughter] Just like, here's Tyler. He
talks to his mom now. There you go.
There's Tyler. There's Here's
here's Brian. He's an active listener.
Congrats on the engagement. I'm so happy
for you two. You know, [laughter]
>> I don't know. I'm exhausted. Being a
woman is is it's enough work being a
woman. It's like we all we do is get
ready. [laughter]
We all we all got ready tonight. We all
got ready. And when the day ends, we go
home and get ready for bed. [laughter]
Do you understand? Every night it's an
hour out of my life. When the sun sets,
I just lock myself in my bathroom and
wash off product with more product
[laughter] and sigh myself to sleep.
It's the worst. I have never seen a
straight man get ready for bed.
[laughter]
You guys just pee, pass out, wake up,
and get promoted.
>> I hate you [cheering] guys.
Don't clap at your privilege in front of
me.
>> You guys are the worst. It's like we're
while the women are getting ready, you
guys are like waiting for us in bed just
like kind of hopeful, you know? Like
maybe she'll blow me when she's done.
It's like no, I won't. [laughter]
I'm not going to let you cream my face
after I've already
[laughter]
Don't do it. Don't blow him tonight.
Don't do it. Don't do it.
Sorry, I don't even know you guys. I'm
[laughter] sorry.
Okay, I think I have to go. I think I
need to leave and go to sleep. Okay, I
have to go. But I um I don't know. I'll
be fine. I'm trying to work on myself.
I'm trying to eat healthier, you know,
be do the healthy thing. I've lost a
little bit of weight, but I still like I
can't shake that feeling of like being
insecure about my body. It's really hard
to get rid of that. Like I if I have to
wear a bikini in public, I have to like
mentally prepare. Like I I honestly
think people will heckle my body at the
like BOO GET OFF THE SAND.
SHE DIDN'T PREPARE, you know? Like I But
you know, I went to the beach recently
and it was totally fine. Great day. No
one made me feel uncomfortable. No one
made me feel bad about my body. It was
all in my head. This fear, you know. So,
I realized something in that moment that
I want to share with you all just for
inspiration. I think this will make you
feel better.
No one cares about you.
[laughter]
Isn't that nice? I'm trying to help you
guys. Okay? Just remember the next time
you're feeling down, just remember I
told you that [laughter]
you don't matter to other people,
okay? But you matter to me. You know,
I've I've been Chinese. I've had a great
time. I love you guys.
>> Goodbye. [cheering] Thank you.
>> HOW Y'ALL DOING? GOOD.
>> ALL RIGHT. What's up, Indian people?
Right. Right in the center. Good. Thank
you for coming out. That makes me feel
safe. [laughter]
That is how I start shows. I just look
for people who look like me. And I think
that's normal, right? When a brown guy
walks into a room, he's going to think,
"Are there brown people here?" When a
black guy walks into a room, he's going
to think, "Are there black people here?"
When a white guy walks into a room, he's
going to think, "Are there black people
here?" Right? [laughter]
A lot of stereotypes about being brown,
people are like, "Oh, you're brown, so
it must be tough to fly being brown."
It's like, "No, it's not that tough. You
know what's tough is to see what hot
white women can get away with at the
airport." My fiance is a white woman.
One time we were traveling, she packed
an entire bottle of shampoo in her
carry-on. The TS agent took her bag,
took the shampoo out. He said, "Ma'am,
you know, I can't let you through with
this." And then she made direct eye
contact with him and said, "Why do you
think it's a bomb?" [laughter]
I was already getting patted down like,
"Becky is going to get me killed." And
then she doubled down. She was like, "Is
that what you think? It's a shampoo
bomb." H a coconut smelling shampoo
bomb. And then, no joke, the TSA agent
just laughed and said, "You right?" And
then gave HER THE SHAMPOO BAG.
If you ask me a question at the airport,
I'm like, "Sir, yes, sir. I love this
country. [laughter] And then I start
yelling the pledge of allegiance. Okay.
I say, I pledge allegiance to the flag.
There's less than three ounces in my
bag. That's what I say. [laughter]
People make all sorts of assumptions
when they find out I'm dating a white
girl. They're like, "Oh, was her family
racist?" It's like, "No." You know
what's interesting? The most racism I've
ever experienced when I was dating was
actually dating another Indian girl.
Okay? Like, uh, like I'm Muslim. Uh, I
was raised Muslim, but now, you know,
occasionally I drink and I smoke and I
mess around. Yeah. I don't eat pork
though because I'm not some sort of
infidel. Okay.
I was dating this Hindu girl in college
and I leaned in a kiss as Hindug third
date. She stopped me. She goes, "No, no,
no, no BMWs." And I was like, "What does
that mean? I drive a Honda Civic."
She was like, "No, no BMWs. That's my
dad's abbreviation. It means no blacks,
Muslims, or whites."
>> And I was so hurt because I was like,
"How come the Mexicans get a free pass?"
You like there's one M and Muslims take
it. That's not fair. M should be
miscellaneous. [laughter] So Jose can
smash but Hussein has to go home. I
don't like that.
I don't like stereotypes, men. I don't
like any stereotype. Here's a stereotype
you hear. Women can't drive. You ever
hear that? Women can't drive. I don't
think that's fair or true. I do feel
safe saying maybe. Hear me out. Women
might not be that great at parking. Hear
[laughter] me out. I think it's
biological. I think men on average are
better at parking because we know how to
take an extension of ourselves and guide
it into some narrow boundaries.
And if you go to the left or the right
of the boundary, you could really ruin
the vibe. [laughter]
So men know we take a wide turn and we
slide in there. And that's why I think a
lot of women aren't that great at
parking cuz I think deep deep down
they're thinking, "Hey, I'll just lay
here and the car will park itself.
Come on, car park. I have places to go.
That's why I don't like self-p parking
cars. Okay, these are the vibrators of
automobiles.
And when I say women, by the way, I'm
talking about straight women. All right,
lesbians, guess what? They can park.
They can park my car better than me.
[laughter]
I'm happy to be here. I flew in from
Atlanta. I grew up in Atlanta. I love
Atlanta. Uh I like learning about
Atlanta's history. Like I was learning
about the civil rights movement. I was
learning about Martin Luther King. You
guys want to know a fun fact? Martin
Luther King was 5'7. It's interesting.
Martin Luther Short King. That's what I
call him. And let me tell you something.
As a 5'8 guy, I do understand why he was
nonviolent. [laughter]
Because I feel like your propensity for
violence is directly proportional to
your height. And I looked it up. Did you
guys know that Malcolm X was 6'4?
That adds up. Malcolm X was like, "We
must use force if necessary." Dr. King
was like, "Or we use our words.
Maybe instead of fighting, we march for
a very long time [laughter]
because my cardio is fantastic."
The best part about living in Atlanta is
that the probability of getting a
compliment from a black woman is very
high. And I know this is racist, but a
compliment from a black lady just means
more. I don't know why, but if a white
lady compliments me, I'm like, "Oh, good
for her. She's having a good day. If a
black lady compliments me, in my soul,
I'm like, "Yo, I earned that shit." All
right. All cancel therapy. I'll be like,
"Hey, Dr. Cohen, this is over because
Gloria told me my fit is fresh as hell."
Black women don't even try when they
compliment you. They'll just pick one
thing about you. They'll turn it into a
compliment. They'll come up to me and be
like, "Okay, glasses. I see you
glasses."
And I'm just smiling like a dumbass
like, "Yeah, you know me. You know I
wear glasses.
You know, I can't see.
[laughter]
That's the kind of positivity we need
nowadays, man. Nowadays, everybody's so
fighting. Everybody's divided
politically, right versus left. You got
to focus on the similarities, you know?
Like, here's something that can bring
Democrats and Republicans together is
that all three of our last presidents,
Trump, Obama, and Biden, all three of
them killed major terrorist leaders in
office. Which just means that when the
approval ratings start to drop, the
president picks up a phone and is like,
"Yo, we got to kill a terrorist ASAP."
And [laughter] it needs to be a brown
one, okay? We need to bring this country
together. And the more Muslim sounding
name, the better. [laughter]
Trump killed a man named Abu Bakr
al-Bakdadi.
You just know when Trump heard that
name, he was like, "Mashallah,
that name it's provocative. Gets the
people going. Send the drones.
[laughter]
I love when a president kills a
terrorist. My favorite was when Obama
killed Bin Laden. You remember when
Obama killed Bin Laden? That was
awesome. My nephew was very young at the
time and he called me and he was like,
"I can't believe Obama actually killed
him." And I was like, "Yeah." And he was
like, "I can't believe Obama actually
killed him." And I realized he thought
Obama killed him.
They were in a dark alley. It was
raining. Obama [laughter] had a gun. He
was like, "This ends now. Our names are
too similar." [laughter]
And I was like, "Obama didn't actually
kill him." And he said, "So who killed
him?" And I said, "Seal team six." He
didn't know what that meant. And he
said, "Like from the zoo."
I was like, "Yes, buddy. Six seals.
Three walruses and the penguins from
Madagascar. They went to Pakistan and
they killed Osama bin Laden."
[laughter]
But you know, no matter what happens
with this country, I'm patriotic. I will
always be patriotic cuz I was born in
this country. I have a US passport. And
when you look like me, that is a
superpower. Like I love traveling to
other countries cuz when I go to another
country's immigration, they see my brown
face. They don't know I'm American. And
they treat me like another foreigner.
And you know what? I play into it.
They're like, "Sir, this way." I'm like,
"Yes, this way." [laughter] They're
like, "Sir, look up here." I'm like,
"Oh, up here." Then they're like, "Sir,
passport." And then I just slammed that
blue passport down with that big gold
eagle on. I'm like, "Hey yo, [\h__\h] say
something, bro. What's up? What's up,
Thailand? We got a problem." I yell,
"This is America." When I throw down the
passport, that's what I yell. And then
when I fly back into the country, I get
randomly selected and I'm like, "This is
also America.
Both things can be America."
I get patriotic about little things, you
know? I get patriotic about cars. Like
my fiance and I were test driving new
cars. We test drove a Lexus, which is a
Japanese car, and I learned that you can
find out a lot about a country based on
the cars that they make. Like, if you
don't put your seatelt on in a Lexus, it
beeps for like 20 minutes, which is a
very Asian response. These are the
rules. You must follow the rules. Try
not putting your seatelt on in a Ford
F-150. It beeps for like 5 seconds, then
it's like, you know what? [\h__\h] it.
[laughter] This is an American car, and
you have the right to go flying straight
through the windshield. Okay.
And yeah, you have no health insurance,
but you'll be okay because you're built
Ford tough.
You know what's crazy? If you drive a
German car and you don't comply with
orders, the car actually pulls over and
then it kills you. Isn't that crazy?
[laughter] Little history joke.
I love learning about history. I like
learning about religion. Clap if you're
raised religious out of curiosity. Yeah.
All right. I was thinking about this the
other day. I was thinking about the
prophets. How come in any religious text
there's like no female prophets? Barely
any female prophets. Is it because God
is sexist? Maybe. But I think I know
why. I think it's because only men have
the delusional confidence that it takes
to become a prophet. I think a woman
hears the voice of God and is LIKE,
"WHAT THE HELL IS HAPPENING? AM I LOSING
my mind?" Maybe she has a glass of wine.
She tells a friend, but a man a man will
hear the voice of God and be like,
"Gather around.
I AM THE CHOSEN ONE." YOU'RE LIKE, "WHAT
about that lady? That lady can speak to
God and he's like, [laughter]
that's a witch." Okay, we should burn
her. God told me to. [laughter]
Here's the thing about religion. I don't
think I'd mind hell. Cuz you know what
hell is in any religious text? It's just
hot. Very toasty in hell. Heaven,
perfect temperature. Nobody's ever
sweating in heaven. And I thought about
it and that makes sense cuz all those
religions started in the Middle East. It
was so damn hot there to begin with that
it was easy for somebody to be like, "Do
you want more of this after you die?"
[laughter] No. Right. Then pray to God.
Pray to GOD FOR A BREEZE.
SO THAT'S WHAT religion was for
centuries was good temperature. Good
temperature. Good temperature.
[laughter]
One day we'll have good temperature. And
then one day humans figured out how to
control the temperature indoors. And
that's when religion went downhill.
[laughter]
And I looked it up. Do you want to know
when modern atheism began?
>> 1900.
>> You know what else was invented in the
year 1900?
>> THE AIR CONDITIONER. THAT'S RIGHT. The
first guy to use a thermostat was like
69, 68, 67. Woo. God is dead. We are all
alone. The air conditioner. THAT'S THE
MOST IMPORTANT MOMENT IN HUMAN HISTORY.
THAT AND THE BIRTH of Christ. Those are
the two most important moments. And
that's how we should measure time. Two
sections BC and AC. But that's just what
I do. That's it for me. Thank you so
much. My name is Zane Sh. [cheering]
>> Is anybody doing okay?
Anybody at all? Anyone crushing it
financially?
[\h__\h] yeah, dude.
Anybody have a ton of money in this
room? They never want us to know
[laughter]
cuz we'll [\h__\h] rob you.
Oh, I don't know. I'm so bad with money.
I'm so bad with money. This is my main
issue with money. I was just like, where
is it? [laughter]
Who the [\h__\h] has it, dude? I don't need
a ton. I'm not crazy. I just need like
enough, you know? Like, I work. You
know, you're at my job right now. Um,
[laughter] thank you for visiting me at
work. I work. I'll get, you know, some
money for this. And then like I don't
[\h__\h] know where it's going to go.
[laughter]
You couldn't pay me to tell you what I'm
going to spend it on. And you shouldn't
cuz I'll spend that, too.
I just I'm so bad with money. I have bad
habits. I spend money on stupid [\h__\h]
you know? Like I live in LA and I keep
um paying for lemons.
That's insane behavior. It's like buying
a dandelion down here. [laughter]
Like why am I paying for something that
it's in my backyard? I mean, it's in my
neighbors backyards.
Okay. I can't. All right. I live on the
edge of Beverly Hills and I started
clocking all the houses with the good
lemon trees. Um, you have never felt a
class divide in your life like the one
you will feel getting caught trying to
take your neighbor's fruit. Okay.
[laughter]
Cuz I go I go in under the cover of
night, you know? And then it it it's
like a biblical level of poverty. Like I
thought this woman could come out of her
house legally and cut my hands off. Um,
I got caught and I was like, "Ah, hi.
I'm your neighbor." Kind of. Um, I
thought I could have a couple of your
fruits. And she was like, "Get out of
here. Those are for the raccoons." Um,
no. [laughter]
Rich people are so wild. I'm like, they
call it trespassing. I call it sharing.
Um, [laughter]
I have I know my biggest bad spending
habit. Um, you know, I do this job. We
travel a lot. Sometimes the comedy club
will put us up in a neighborhood with a
bunch of cute [\h__\h] shops. I'm sorry.
I'm a white lady. I got to go to the
shops. I can't stop buying knickknacks,
chop keys, trinkets, you know, dumb
[\h__\h] pieces of [\h__\h] you know? Just
like cute little stupid ass [\h__\h]
pieces of [\h__\h] just [laughter] like the
dumbest little [\h__\h] Oh, I can't stop
and I don't have any money and I can't
stop doing it. I got to go to the shops
and I got to get the [\h__\h] because
life is very painful. [laughter]
It's really hard to be alive. You know
what I mean? So, if I feel a little bit
better for a while buying a [\h__\h]
ceramic rabbit with a cowboy hat on,
[laughter]
smoking a carrot like it's a cigar, I'm
going to [\h__\h] buy it. Okay? I'm going
to buy it. I'm going to bubble wrap it.
I'm going to put it in my suitcase. I'm
going to fly it home. I'm going put it
on a shelf and never [\h__\h] think about
it again. [laughter]
There's a name for this now. I learned
it from Tik Tok. It's called dopamine
shopping. Like, that's what it is, you
know? It's like you get a little zap of
dopamine, you buy something cute. And I
I can't believe I'm still doing this
because like I also do drugs. So,
[laughter] what's going to work, you
know?
I'm not proud of myself, but I was on
one of these trips. So, I was on a cute
little street with a bunch of cute chops
and I had again very ashamed, but I had
um $60 in my bank account and I spent
$45 on a hat with a little hot dog on
it. [laughter] Is hot dog embroidered
and tiny as [\h__\h] You [\h__\h] bet it is,
dude. And I get these are the decisions
you can make when you don't have kids,
you know, cuz I don't have to get home
from the road and be like, "Sorry,
honey. No lunch money this week, but you
can wear this sick ass hot dog hat to
school. [laughter]
I was on one of these cute streets with
my remaining $15. I went into a
children's toy store to buy a stuffed
gator for my dog.
I go up to the counter with a stuffed
gator for my dog and um and the lady
goes, "Is this for your baby?" And I
said, "Yeah."
And she goes, "What's your baby's name?"
I go, "Ruby." She's like, "How old is
she?" I go, she's 10. And she was like,
"Oh, we have some really good kids books
in the corner if you're interested." I
go, "Oh, she can't read yet." Um,
we're really working on it. [laughter]
Um, now I know I look like just a fresh
angelic newborn baby. Um, but I am
currently in pmenopause.
[laughter]
[cheering] Yeah, I don't I'm in it. I'm
in penmenopause. Don't get scared. It's
not the big one. [laughter] It's just
like menopause's like hot cool little
sister, you know what I mean? Like Perry
like like she like lives into Panga
Canyon and like raises bees, you know?
She's like Perry. Like it's chill. Um
Perry menopause. I don't I guess it was
invented 2 years ago. I don't know.
[laughter]
Well, I think it started when I got it.
Nobody ever [\h__\h] told us anything
about this and then it just hits you,
you know? So, I'm in it. And you know,
it's a gnarly thing because we say that.
We say we're in it. We say I'm in
pmenopause. I'm in menopause. There's no
other medical condition that we say that
for. You don't say I I'm in cancer.
Right. Right. You don't say I'm in
syphilis. Right. What do you say?
[laughter] You say I have What do you
say when you talk about it? I
[laughter and applause] like I'm dealing
with syphilis or whatever.
I'm in I'm in pmenopause.
The inn really implies a sort of
imminent danger. Do you know what I
mean? Like I'm in prison. Um I was in
Vietnam. I'm in a Waffle House. You know
[laughter]
scary. It's like the Guantanamo of
hormonal conditions. Um [laughter]
I'm in it. I'm doing it. Nobody [\h__\h]
ever told us a goddamn thing. Uh, I I
think it's on purpose, you know, because
how [\h__\h] crazy would you be acting in
your 20s if you knew it was coming? But
I'm here from the future to tell you
[laughter] it's a nightmare. Um, every
day is a new fresh hell, learning about
a new symptom, okay? Itchy ears, blurry
vision, and they let us drive. Isn't
that crazy?
>> [laughter]
>> Next time you see like a mid-40s [\h__\h]
on the highway, just know every single
hole on her body, something's up.
[laughter]
Something's off.
Frozen shoulder. Y'all heard about that
one. [laughter] Let me tell you right
now, all of you are taking your
shoulders for granted. I didn't even
know I ever used my shoulders for what?
Maybe close the fridge. I don't know.
Like [laughter]
push through a concert. Um,
when they freeze up, you notice, you
know what I mean? Like it's it's exactly
what it sounds like. Your shoulders just
stop working sometimes. Why have you
ever heard of this?
She's in it. Um, [laughter] she's in it.
She's in hell.
This can start as early as 27, by the
way. So, just [\h__\h] watch it coming.
And you know that tired old argument of
like, oh, we can't have a woman
president because like what if she's
like in menopause and then she like
pushes the big red button or whatever?
Like let me tell you, that shoulder is
going to lock up. We'll be fine.
[laughter]
We'll be much safer.
This is for sure the scariest one. The
scariest [\h__\h] one. [laughter]
I'm so sorry.
your labia
can and will start to just slowly absorb
back into your body. Clap if you've
heard of this.
Exactly. Because they don't want us to
know. Because if we were in high school
health class and they told teenage
girls, "Hey, you're going to lose some
of that." You wouldn't put up We
wouldn't put up with anything in our
20s. We're [\h__\h] storming into our
boss's office like, "Uh, no, Dan, you're
going to give me a raise cuz I got two
full juicy lips right now and I'm not
doing this." [laughter]
Well, if my shoulders work,
no one mentioned anything. I did the
math and I lived with my mom when she
was my age and I was 14. There's no day
I can remember that my mom like came
home from work and I was like, "How you
feeling?" And she was just like, "My
[\h__\h] lips. [laughter]
It looks like somebody poured table salt
on two slugs." Um, [laughter]
mine are okay so far. I check every day.
[laughter]
Um, and I have various young men check
as well. Um,
some stuff's starting to make more
sense. You know what I mean? Some things
are kind of clicking. Like I remember
when I was a kid, like my grandma would
always like tell me I was getting too
lippy. And now I know she's a jealous.
[laughter]
I [\h__\h] hate her, dude.
You know what it's doing to me? It's
start like going through this process as
a woman, it's starting to make me
believe in the Bible again. Like I grew
up Baptist, you know, I believed all of
it. But even when I believed all of it
as a strict Christian, I still always
took issue with like the story of Eve,
you know what I mean? Cuz they blamed
everything on her. Like it was so
sexist. Like literally grown men would
look at us adolescent girls and be like,
"Oh, you don't like your period? Well,
you have one [\h__\h] to blame for that."
[laughter]
Yeah. No, they would go behind the
pulpit and be like, "This stupid [\h__\h]
this [\h__\h] naked [\h__\h] with her big
old bush had to eat the fruit." And now
we have bad stuff in the world like, you
know, war and murder and Bill Mah.
[laughter]
They blamed everything on her and I was
always against it and now I'm sort of
like I'm going through it and I do feel
cursed. I'm like why'd you have to eat
that [\h__\h] apple, [\h__\h] [laughter]
You you needed a snack. You're listening
to snakes and now my shoulder's locked
up. [laughter]
We didn't get enough um information in
the Bible about like their relationship
after the fruit. [laughter]
Like we know about Adam and Eve's like
kids and stuff, but I want to know like
more behind the scenes of their
marriage. Like do you think Eve ever won
an argument again?
You think they're just chilling in the
garden? And she's like, "Adam, you're
being kind of annoying." He's like, "Oh,
I'm being annoying."
[laughter] Oh, I'm sorry. We have child
molesters cuz you needed a little snack.
[laughter]
I um Okay, wait. I got to do one more
minute. Brad.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. So fast. Okay. No, you're not
Brad. Shut the [\h__\h] up. [laughter]
Be quiet, syphilis man. UM
[laughter]
OH, I I I love this job so much. I truly
love this job. I uh there's one part of
it I just don't want to do anymore in my
life, and that's just like get ready.
[laughter] Anyone else tired of getting
dressed every godamn day? Every day.
Like what? Every day life if you're
lucky is you like you got to like figure
out what you're gonna eat and then you
gota like put on a little outfit like a
[\h__\h] cabbage patch kid. I don't want
to do it anymore.
And I never I never thought this long
into standup that I would want to be a
dude standup comic. And I don't. But I
would love to come to work every night
looking like [\h__\h] And they get to do
that. You saw him. [laughter]
No effort. [applause] no effort
whatsoever. It's different for us, you
know, women is if I came up here with
just like no makeup and sweats, you'd be
like, "Oh no, I think this lady is in
cancer." Um, [laughter]
I have a special relationship to
clothes, unlike some of you, you know,
cuz I am, you know, I'm kind of a fat
[\h__\h] And [laughter]
no, like not in the Midwest, but
in LA [laughter] where I'm the fattest
[\h__\h] in town
and I'm used to it. It's cute. I don't
care. Is anyone else here like a little
bit of a fat [\h__\h] [laughter]
Okay. Interesting. You're lying. And
thank you for the two woos over here.
This is so [\h__\h] wild because I
appreciate you, but like I'm in here and
I have working eyes and there's like a
bunch of fat [\h__\h] in this room. But
[laughter]
it's a journey. It's a journey to
confidence and you're not there. And I
understand.
>> Not just a fat [\h__\h] got big stupid
titties. Thank you so much.
Yeah, but it's the whole thing. I got to
strap them into this [\h__\h] every day. And
it's like, you know, when you have big
titties, it's a different process.
Putting on a bra from small I've seen
small titted women. You're so cute. You
You're like I just clicked on my bra. I
just clicked it [laughter]
like coffee in one hand. I was on a
call.
Big production when you have big
titties. Okay. So, we got to do this
thing where we start the bra at the
back. [laughter] You know, we got to get
like a heavy rotation going on, like a
lot of centrifugal force. [laughter]
Okay. And we all have rug burn on our
[\h__\h] ribs. And then and then you get
to the front, you got to do the flap and
scoop. You got to do the flap and scoop.
[laughter] You're getting everything in
there. All of a sudden, you're pushing
other parts of your body into the bra
that are not tit at all. Okay.
[laughter] Little net, little back,
little [\h__\h] little crack. Honestly,
my tits are great tonight. And it's
mostly armpit. And I did that for you
all. I did that for you. Thank you so
much.
>> [music]